<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<?metadataRepository version='1.1.0'?>
<repository name='update site: http://altd.borland.com/update/eclipse3.5/' type='org.eclipse.equinox.internal.p2.metadata.repository.LocalMetadataRepository' version='1'>
  <properties size='2'>
    <property name='p2.timestamp' value='1532620220648'/>
    <property name='site.checksum' value='3581101426'/>
  </properties>
  <references size='2'>
    <repository uri='http://altd.borland.com/update/eclipse3.5/site.xml' url='http://altd.borland.com/update/eclipse3.5/site.xml' type='1' options='0'/>
    <repository uri='http://altd.borland.com/update/eclipse3.5/site.xml' url='http://altd.borland.com/update/eclipse3.5/site.xml' type='0' options='0'/>
  </references>
  <units size='11'>
    <unit id='com.borland.team.starteam.ui.integration' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.borland.team.starteam.ui.integration' range='[0.0.0,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.team.starteam.ui.integration' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.borland.team.starteam.ui.integration' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.borland.team.starteam.ui.integration' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.borland.team.starteam.ui.integration&#xA;Bundle-Version: 11.0.0.97v20111028-1643&#xA;Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.borland.team.starteam.provider' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.borland.team.starteam.provider' range='[0.0.0,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.team.starteam.provider' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.borland.team.starteam.provider' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.borland.team.starteam.provider' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.borland.team.starteam.provider&#xA;Bundle-Version: 11.0.0.97v20111028-1643&#xA;Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.borland.starteam.sdk.native' version='11.0.0.73' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.borland.starteam.sdk.native' range='[0.0.0,11.0.0.73)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam.sdk.native' version='11.0.0.73'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.borland.starteam.sdk.native' version='11.0.0.73'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.borland.starteam.sdk.native' version='11.0.0.73'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='2'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.borland.starteam.sdk.native&#xA;Bundle-Version: 11.0.0.73&#xA;Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.borland.starteam_3.5.feature.jar' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'>
      <properties size='10'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%label'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='Borland Software Corporation'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.update.feature.application' value='org.eclipse.ui.ide.workbench'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.update.feature.plugin' value='com.borland.team.starteam.ui.integration'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.update.feature.primary' value='true'/>
        <property name='df_LT.label' value='StarTeam 2009 R2 Eclipse 3.5 Client'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright© 1998-2010 Borland Software Corporation. All rights reserved. All patents pending.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='StarTeam team provider, including StarTeam SDK plug-in.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='Borland StarTeam 2009 R2 End User License Agreement&#xA;IMPORTANT: LICENSOR IS PROVIDING THIS SOFTWARE FOR YOUR USE SUBJECT TO &#xA;YOUR AGREEMENT TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW.  IF &#xA;YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT BY CLICKING ON SETUP&apos;S ACCEPT &#xA;BUTTON, YOU WILL NOT BE ABLE TO USE THE SOFTWARE.  BY CLICKING SETUP&apos;S ACCEPT &#xA;BUTTON YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THIS AGREEMENT, UNDERSTOOD IT, AND &#xA;AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ITS TERMS AND CONDITIONS.&#xA;END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;WHEREAS, Licensor desires to grant to Licensee, and Licensee desires to &#xA;accept from Licensor, a license to use Licensed Software (as defined herein) &#xA;upon the terms and conditions hereinafter set forth; NOW, THEREFORE, Licensor &#xA;and Licensee agree as follows:&#xA;For this End User License Agreement (&apos;License &#xA;Agreement&apos;) the following terms shall have the meanings given &#xA;below:&#xA;&apos;Blades&apos; means multiple server modules housed &#xA;in a single chassis each with its own CPU, hard disk and memory.  &#xA;&apos;Core&apos; means a single unit of processing within &#xA;a computer chip, comprising an arithmetic logic unit, registers, instruction &#xA;fetcher and data fetcher/storer. &apos;CPU&apos; (Central Processor Unit) &#xA;means a data processing unit, normally identified with a single microchip &#xA;mounted on a single circuit board and can comprise several Cores. A computer &#xA;&apos;box&apos; can contain several CPUs. The &apos;box&apos; is sometimes &#xA;referred to as a &apos;server&apos; or a &apos;machine&apos; (or possibly a &#xA;&apos;mainframe&apos;).&#xA;&apos;Licensor&apos; means the Licensor identified in the &#xA;printed End User License Agreement which is (i) included with and/or &#xA;accompanies the program package incorporating this Licensed Software &#xA;delivered to Licensee or (ii) attached to and/or supplied with the electronic &#xA;program download incorporating this Licensed Software delivered to Licensee, &#xA;as appropriate.&#xA;&apos;Licensed Software&apos; means the object code &#xA;version of the Licensor computer programs, their accompanying user &#xA;documentation (&apos;Documentation&apos;) and other supplemental materials as &#xA;provided to Licensee by Licensor, including but not limited to any software &#xA;security keys, modifications or additions relating thereto. The Licensed &#xA;Software shall also include any new releases, updates, revisions, &#xA;modifications, additions, corrections and fixes of the Licensed Software that &#xA;Licensee receives under Sections 6 and 7 below or under maintenance for which &#xA;Licensee has separately contracted and paid. From commencement of this &#xA;License Agreement, the &apos;Licensed Software&apos; shall also include, and &#xA;this License Agreement shall apply to, any prior versions of the Licensed &#xA;Software licensed by Licensee. This License Agreement does not grant Licensee &#xA;the right to any new releases, updates, revisions, modifications, additions, &#xA;corrections and fixes of the Licensed Software unless provided by Licensor &#xA;under Section 6 below. Licensed Software products are available to operate on &#xA;the Windows, Linux, Unix or other computer platforms and a separate license &#xA;is required for a Licensed Software product for each computer platform.&#xA;&apos;Product Order&apos; means a document that has been &#xA;(i) executed by Licensee, describing each Licensed Software license purchased &#xA;and (ii) accepted by Licensor or its authorized distributors.  Licensor will &#xA;accept the Product Order by either confirming Licensor&apos;s acceptance in &#xA;writing or by delivering the Licensed Software Licensee, whichever occurs &#xA;first.  Each Product Order shall constitute a separate agreement and shall &#xA;incorporate therein all of the terms and conditions of this License &#xA;Agreement.  In the event of any conflict between the terms of this License &#xA;Agreement and the terms of any Product Order which have been expressly &#xA;accepted by a duly authorized signatory of Licensor in writing, such terms of &#xA;the Product Order shall govern.  In no event shall any terms and conditions &#xA;of Licensee contained in a purchase order or similar document issued by &#xA;Licensee in connection with this License Agreement or a Product Order apply &#xA;and any such document issued shall be only for the administrative purposes of &#xA;identifying the Licensed Software ordered, the number of licenses, and the &#xA;price to be paid and shall have no other legal effect.&#xA;&apos;Disaster Recovery System&apos; is defined as a &#xA;computer system that is used (i) if a disaster arises and the original &#xA;production system is unavailable, (ii) for the purposes of disaster recovery &#xA;testing and/or (iii) for system diagnostics or maintenance of the Disaster &#xA;Recovery System itself. A Disaster Recovery System does not include any &#xA;system that is in the same computer cluster as the machine on which the &#xA;development or production copy of the Licensed Software is installed.&#xA;&apos;Virtual Machine&apos; means a software &#xA;implementation that executes programs like a physical machine where the &#xA;software running inside the virtual machine is limited to the resources and &#xA;abstractions provided by the virtual machine. &#xA;1 GRANT OF LICENSE.  For payment of the applicable non-&#xA;refundable license fees identified on the Product Order, Licensor grants &#xA;solely to Licensee, as an end user, a personal, perpetual, non-transferable, &#xA;non-sublicensable and non-exclusive license to use the Licensed Software &#xA;subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this License Agreement.  &#xA;Licensee shall have the right to use the Licensed Software solely for its own &#xA;internal use and benefit. For the avoidance of doubt, the license granted &#xA;herein does not permit (i) third party contractors (including without &#xA;limitation outsourcers) to access or use the Licensed Software for Licensee&apos;s &#xA;internal use and benefit without the prior written consent of Licensor and &#xA;the payment of an additional license fee, (ii) the public to access or use &#xA;the Licensed Software (including without limitation, via the internet) except &#xA;as specifically provided in Annex 1 hereunder, and/or (iii) installation, use &#xA;or access of the Licensed Software on, in, or from a Virtual Machine except &#xA;as specifically provided in Annex 1 or Annex 2 hereunder.  Where permitted by &#xA;Licensor pursuant to sections 1(i) and (ii) hereof, Licensee shall be liable &#xA;to Licensor in respect of any breach of this License Agreement resulting from &#xA;any access or use by third party contractors and/or the public.  Access &#xA;and/or use of data, results and/or output obtained and/or generated, either &#xA;directly or indirectly, through the use of any Licensed Software are deemed &#xA;to be access and/or use of such Licensed Software and such data, results &#xA;and/or output shall be subject to the licensing terms and restrictions &#xA;applicable to such Licensed Software.  Different license options are &#xA;available from Licensor as set forth or referred to in Annex 1 (&apos;License &#xA;Option(s)&apos;), although not all License Options are available for each &#xA;specific Licensed Software product. The applicable License Option to be &#xA;purchased by Licensee for the Licensed Software shall be identified in the &#xA;Product Order. Additional License Options (as appropriate) are required to be &#xA;purchased by Licensee for use of the Licensed Software on a Disaster Recovery &#xA;System or for load-balancing, fail-over, training, or testing purposes.  &#xA;Licensed Software purchased for testing purposes will be subject to the Test &#xA;License Option terms and restrictions set forth in Annex 1.C.  Certain &#xA;Licensed Software may also be subject to additional terms and conditions as &#xA;set forth in the &apos;Specific Software Terms&apos; located in Annex 2. The &#xA;Specific Software Terms will prevail in the event of any conflict. &#xA;2 USER RESTRICTION.  Licensee agrees not to:&#xA;2.1&#x9;Copy and distribute the Licensed Software, in whole or in part, &#xA;for internal use without paying Licensor the applicable additional fees, &#xA;except (i) for making a reasonable number of archival back-up copies; or (ii) &#xA;as expressly authorized by Licensor in writing; or (iii) for making a &#xA;reasonable number of copies of the Documentation supplied to Licensee by &#xA;Licensor in electronic form.  Licensee shall reproduce and affix all &#xA;copyright and other proprietary rights notices appearing in or on the &#xA;Licensed Software, including the notices of all third party suppliers and all &#xA;those included in any Third Party Software, as defined below in all such &#xA;copies thereof.&#xA;2.2&#x9;Copy and/or distribute the Licensed Software, in whole or in &#xA;part, to third parties without first entering into a separate distribution &#xA;license agreement with Licensor or permit use or access to all or part of the &#xA;Licensed Software to any third party except as specifically provided in Annex &#xA;1 hereunder. For the avoidance of doubt, third party(ies) include without &#xA;limitation contractors, outsourcers, Licensee&apos;s customers and the public.&#xA;2.3&#x9;Transfer, ship or use the Licensed Software outside the continent &#xA;in which it was originally licensed to Licensee, except as otherwise &#xA;specified in Annex 1 and/or Annex 2.&#xA;2.4&#x9;Install, access or use the Licensed Software on an operating &#xA;system other than the operating system for which the Licensed Software was &#xA;originally licensed to Licensee, except as otherwise specified in Annex 1 &#xA;and/or Annex 2.&#xA;2.5&#x9;Assign, sell, rent, lease, lend, sublicense, outsource or &#xA;otherwise transfer the Licensed Software to any third party, or authorize or &#xA;appoint any third party to do so.&#xA;2.6&#x9;Use the Licensed Software for timesharing, facilities management, &#xA;outsourcing, hosting, service bureau use, other data processing services to &#xA;third parties or like purposes.&#xA;2.7&#x9;Modify the Licensed Software or provide any person with the means &#xA;to do the same. &#xA;2.8&#x9;Create derivative works, translate, disassemble, recompile or &#xA;reverse engineer any Licensed Software or attempt to do so (except to the &#xA;extent applicable law specifically permits such activity).&#xA;2.9&#x9;Alter, destroy, or otherwise remove any proprietary notices or &#xA;labels on or embedded within the Licensed Software or Documentation.&#xA;2.10&#x9;Utilize for itself, or permit any third party to utilize, any &#xA;software application program created, in whole or in part, utilizing any &#xA;Licensed Software without a valid and properly granted Deployment Product &#xA;License.&#xA;2.11&#x9;Use the Licensed Software in a manner other than as specifically &#xA;permitted in this License Agreement.&#xA;3 AUDITS.  Licensee agrees to (i) keep records of and &#xA;provide the location, model and serial number of any and all machines on &#xA;which the Licensed Software is installed or from which the Licensed Software &#xA;is accessed, and the names of and how many users are accessing the Licensed &#xA;Software, (ii) implement a reasonable mechanism or process to ensure that &#xA;Licensee&apos;s use of the Licensed Software does not exceed the number of &#xA;licenses granted, (iii) take all necessary steps to destroy or erase all &#xA;Licensed Software codes, programs and other proprietary information before &#xA;disposing of any media containing the Licensed Software, and (iv) promptly &#xA;provide written notice to Licensor if Licensee&apos;s usage exceeds the license &#xA;granted.  Upon Licensor&apos;s reasonable request, but not more frequently than &#xA;annually without reasonable cause, Licensee shall furnish Licensor with a &#xA;statement signed by a director and/or auditor, as required by Licensor, &#xA;verifying the above and shall permit Licensor to audit the use of the &#xA;Licensed Software at such times as may be mutually agreed upon.  In the event &#xA;Licensee&apos;s usage exceeds the license granted, without prejudice to any other &#xA;rights or remedies Licensor may have, including without limitation injunctive &#xA;relief, Licensee agrees to pay Licensor the then current license and &#xA;maintenance fees for the use of the additional licenses.  Further, if such &#xA;usage exceeds the license granted by more than five percent (5%), Licensee &#xA;shall also reimburse Licensor for the reasonable cost of such audit in &#xA;addition to other amounts due.&#xA;4 DOCUMENTATION.  One (1) electronic copy of Licensor&apos;s &#xA;standard Documentation, describing Licensor&apos;s recommended use and application &#xA;of the Licensed Software, will be furnished free of additional charge to &#xA;Licensee by Licensor with the Licensed Software.  Printed copies of any &#xA;documentation may be available for purchase from Licensor or its authorized &#xA;distributors.&#xA;5 TERM OF LICENSE.  This License Agreement and Licensee&apos;s &#xA;license for the Licensed Software is perpetual, unless a subscription/term &#xA;license has been purchased by Licensee, and is subject to earlier termination &#xA;as provided in this Section 5.  Licensor may terminate this License Agreement &#xA;and Licensee&apos;s license to the Licensed Software immediately by giving &#xA;Licensee written notice of termination in the event that either (i) Licensee &#xA;breaches any term or condition of this License Agreement and Licensee has &#xA;failed to remedy such breach within ten (10) days of the date of notice from &#xA;Licensor to Licensee or (ii) Licensee is wound up,  has a receiver appointed &#xA;or enters into liquidation or bankruptcy or analogous process or processes in &#xA;Licensee&apos;s home country.  Termination shall be without prejudice to any other &#xA;rights or remedies Licensor may have.  Licensee may at any time terminate &#xA;this License Agreement voluntarily by giving written notice of termination to &#xA;Licensor.  In the event of any termination Licensee will have no right to &#xA;keep or use the Licensed Software or any copy of the Licensed Software for &#xA;any purpose and Licensee shall destroy and erase all copies of such Licensed &#xA;Software in its possession or control, and forward written certification to &#xA;Licensor that all such copies of Licensed Software have been destroyed or &#xA;erased.  &#xA;6 MAINTENANCE.  Where Licensee purchases maintenance &#xA;services, Licensee&apos;s initial maintenance term will begin upon delivery to &#xA;Licensee of the Licensed Software and continue for one (1) year thereafter &#xA;unless otherwise specified in the applicable annual maintenance agreement or &#xA;in the Product Order, or earlier if the license is terminated.  Where &#xA;Licensee purchases maintenance for any Licensed Software product licensed &#xA;hereunder, Licensee hereby agrees that it shall purchase such support &#xA;services for all of Licensee&apos;s licensed copies of such Licensed Software &#xA;product on the relevant computer platform.  Maintenance services provided by &#xA;Licensor will be subject to Licensor&apos;s then current applicable annual &#xA;maintenance agreement unless otherwise agreed by the parties in writing.  &#xA;7 LIMITED WARRANTY.  Licensor warrants for a period of &#xA;ninety (90) days from delivery to Licensee (&apos;Warranty Period&apos;) (i) &#xA;that the media on which the Licensed Software is supplied is free from &#xA;defects in materials or workmanship under normal use and (ii) that the copy &#xA;of the Licensed Software delivered to Licensee conforms in all material &#xA;respects to the Documentation.  As the sole and exclusive remedy for not &#xA;meeting part (i) of the above warranty, Licensor&apos;s sole obligation shall be &#xA;to repair or replace free of charge any defective media on which the Licensed &#xA;Software is delivered if the media is returned to Licensor by Licensee during &#xA;the Warranty Period.  As the sole and exclusive remedy for not meeting part &#xA;(ii) of the above warranty, Licensor shall repair or replace the Licensed &#xA;Software free of charge or if Licensor reasonably determines that such remedy &#xA;is not economically or technically feasible, Licensee shall be entitled to a &#xA;full refund of the license fee and any maintenance fee paid by Licensee with &#xA;respect to that particular Licensed Software and Licensee&apos;s license to use &#xA;such Licensed Software will terminate.  The warranty set forth in this &#xA;Section 7 shall not apply if the defect in the Licensed Software is the &#xA;result of: (a) the Licensed Software not being used in accordance with the &#xA;Documentation, this License Agreement or with the platform(s) for which the &#xA;Licensed Software has been designed and licensed by Licensor; or (b) the &#xA;Licensed Software having been altered, modified or converted by Licensee or &#xA;any third party except as may be specified in the Documentation; or (c) the &#xA;malfunctioning of Licensee&apos;s equipment; or (d) accident or abuse; or (e) &#xA;service by any unauthorized person; or (f) other software used by Licensee &#xA;which has not been provided by Licensor or for which the Licensed Software is &#xA;not designed and licensed for operation; or (g) Third Party Software, as &#xA;defined below; or (h) any other cause occurring after initial delivery of the &#xA;media to Licensee unless caused directly by Licensor.  The foregoing states &#xA;the complete and entire remedies that Licensee has under this warranty.  &#xA;Licensor shall have no responsibility for any warranty claims made outside of &#xA;the Warranty Period.&#xA;8 DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY.  The Licensed Software cannot &#xA;be tested in every possible operating environment, therefore Licensor does &#xA;not warrant that the functions contained in the Licensed Software will meet &#xA;Licensee&apos;s requirements, that operation of the Licensed Software will be &#xA;uninterrupted, or that the Licensed Software is error free.  EXCEPT AS SET &#xA;FORTH HEREIN AND TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, &#xA;EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, &#xA;IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, QUALITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR &#xA;PURPOSE ARE EXCLUDED ON THE PART OF LICENSOR AND ITS THIRD-PARTY SUPPLIERS.  &#xA;Licensee acknowledges that Licensee is responsible for the selection of the &#xA;Licensed Software to achieve Licensee&apos;s intended results and for the &#xA;installation of, use of and results obtained from the Licensed Software.  &#xA;&#xA;9 LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.  ANY LIABILITY OF LICENSOR &#xA;SHALL BE LIMITED IN THE AGGREGATE TO THE AMOUNTS PAID BY LICENSEE FOR THE &#xA;LICENSED SOFTWARE.  THIS LIMITATION APPLIES TO ALL CAUSES OF ACTION, &#xA;INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION BREACH OF CONTRACT, BREACH OF WARRANTY, &#xA;NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, MISREPRESENTATION AND OTHER TORTS.  THE &#xA;LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY DESCRIBED IN THIS SECTION 9 ALSO APPLY TO LICENSOR&apos;S &#xA;THIRD-PARTY SUPPLIERS.  LICENSOR&apos;S AND ITS THIRD-PARTY SUPPLIERS&apos; LIMITATIONS &#xA;OF LIABILITY ARE NOT CUMULATIVE.  Licensee&apos;s remedies in this License &#xA;Agreement are Licensee&apos;s exclusive remedies.&#xA;NEITHER LICENSOR NOR ANY OF ITS THIRD-PARTY SUPPLIERS SHALL BE LIABLE &#xA;FOR ANY INJURY, LOSS OR DAMAGE, WHETHER INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR &#xA;CONSEQUENTIAL NOR FOR ANY LOST PROFITS, CONTRACTS, LOSS OF DATA OR PROGRAMS, &#xA;OR THE COST OF RECOVERING SUCH DATA OR PROGRAMS, EVEN IF INFORMED OF THE &#xA;POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES IN ADVANCE.  &#xA;NEITHER THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT NOR ANYTHING IN THIS SECTION 9 SHALL &#xA;PURPORT TO EXCLUDE OR RESTRICT THE LIABILITY OF LICENSOR OR ITS THIRD-PARTY &#xA;SUPPLIERS TO ANY EXTENT NOT PERMITTED BY LAW.  &#xA;10  HIGH-RISK USES.  The Licensed Software is not fault &#xA;tolerant, nor designed, manufactured or intended for use in hazardous &#xA;environments requiring fail-safe performance (including, without limitation, &#xA;the operation of nuclear facilities, aircraft navigation or communication &#xA;systems, air traffic control, direct life support machines, or weapons &#xA;systems) in which failure of the Licensed Software could lead directly or &#xA;indirectly to death, personal injury or severe physical or environmental &#xA;damage.  Licensor and its suppliers specifically disclaim any express or &#xA;implied warranty of fitness for a particular purpose and shall have no &#xA;liability for any use of the Licensed Software in any high-risk situations. &#xA;&#xA;11 OWNERSHIP.  Licensor (or its affiliates) and where &#xA;applicable Licensor&apos;s third party suppliers have and will retain all &#xA;ownership rights to the Licensed Software, together with any complete or &#xA;partial copies thereof. Such ownership rights include without limitation all &#xA;patent rights, copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, service marks, related &#xA;goodwill, and confidential and proprietary information relating thereto.  &#xA;This License Agreement does not convey any proprietary interest to Licensee &#xA;with respect to the Licensed Software other than the license specified &#xA;herein.  Where the Licensed Software provided under this License Agreement &#xA;contains or is derived from portions of materials provided by a third-party &#xA;supplier under license to Licensor, Licensor has assumed responsibility for &#xA;the selection of such materials and their use in producing the Licensed &#xA;Software and any such third-party suppliers are intended beneficiaries of &#xA;this License Agreement.  &#xA;12 NOTICE TO U.S. GOVERNMENT END USERS.  The Licensed &#xA;Software is provided to the United States Government with RESTRICTED RIGHTS &#xA;and its supporting documentation is provided with LIMITED RIGHTS.  Use, &#xA;duplication, or disclosure by the United States Government is subject to the &#xA;restrictions as set forth in FAR52.227-14 and DFAR252.227-7013 et seq. or the &#xA;successor as appropriate.  Manufacturer is Borland Software Corporation, 8310 &#xA;North Capital of Texas Highway, Building 2, Suite 100, Austin, TX 78731, &#xA;USA.&#xA;13 LICENSE FEES, PAYMENT, AND TERMS.  Licensee agrees to &#xA;pay the applicable end user license fees for the Licensed Software within &#xA;thirty (30) days of the date of invoice or such earlier date as is specified &#xA;in the Product Order.  End user license fees are non-refundable except as &#xA;provided in Section 7 above, or in the Specific Software Terms below, and &#xA;shall be paid without deduction, including without limitation, of any &#xA;withholding tax.  End user license fees are exclusive of any applicable &#xA;transportation charges, value added and other applicable taxes and duties and &#xA;all such amounts shall be paid or reimbursed by Licensee. Late payments shall &#xA;accrue interest at the rate of 1.5% per month compounded or, if lower, the &#xA;maximum rate allowed by law.  &#xA;14 RELATED SERVICES.  Licensee shall be responsible for &#xA;obtaining and installing all proper hardware and support software (including &#xA;operating systems) and for proper installation and implementation of and &#xA;training concerning the Licensed Software.  In the event that Licensee &#xA;retains Licensor to perform any services with respect to the Licensed &#xA;Software (for example: installation, implementation, maintenance, consulting &#xA;and/or training services), Licensee and Licensor agree that such services &#xA;shall be subject to Licensor&apos;s then current standard terms, conditions and &#xA;rates for such services unless otherwise agreed in writing by Licensor.&#xA;15 THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE AND COMPONENTS.  The Licensed &#xA;Software may contain certain named third party software programs that &#xA;Licensee shall license directly from the third party subject to such third &#xA;party&apos;s terms and conditions (for example Adobe Acrobat or Microsoft Internet &#xA;Explorer) (&apos;Third Party Software&apos;).  All Third Party Software is &#xA;provided by the licensor of the Third Party Software and solely under such &#xA;third party&apos;s terms and conditions and not by Licensor.   Therefore the &#xA;obligations, duties and rights of Licensor and Licensee under this License &#xA;Agreement do not apply to such Third Party Software.  Additionally, Licensor &#xA;has embedded certain run time or other elements provided by third party &#xA;suppliers to Licensor (&apos;Third Party Components&apos;). Such Third Party &#xA;Components may also be loaded on the Licensed Software media. Third Party &#xA;Components are licensed to Licensee pursuant to this License Agreement.  &#xA;Licensee may only access Third Party Components of the Licensed Software in &#xA;the course of using the Licensed Software.  Licensee may not make or attempt &#xA;any direct access to any such Third Party Components other than with the &#xA;Licensed Software. The Third-Party Software is the property of its respective &#xA;third party supplier to Licensor.  Such third party suppliers own all copies &#xA;of the Third-Party Software, however made. Licensee agrees not to contest the &#xA;ownership of the Third Party Components nor use any trademark or service mark &#xA;belonging to such third party suppliers. All limitations, restrictions and &#xA;obligations applicable to the Licensed Software set forth in this License &#xA;Agreement shall apply to Licensee&apos;s use of the Third Party Components.  &#xA;Licensee agrees that such third party suppliers are intended third party &#xA;beneficiaries of all terms and conditions of this License Agreement intended &#xA;to protect intellectual property rights in the Licensed Software (including &#xA;the Third Party Components) and limit certain uses thereof.&#xA;16 PRIVACY.  The Licensed Software may contain features &#xA;which may allow Licensee to collect data from, control and/or monitor &#xA;computers running the Licensed Software deployed by Licensee without notice &#xA;to or knowledge by users of the Licensed Software.  Licensee is solely &#xA;responsible for, and assumes all liability with respect to, the collection of &#xA;data with respect to its users of the Licensed Software including, without &#xA;limitation, notifying such users and complying with all data collection, &#xA;privacy and other regulations, laws, industry standards and rights of others &#xA;applicable to any such activity.  Licensee shall indemnify and hold Licensor &#xA;harmless from and against any damages, claims, losses, settlements, &#xA;attorneys&apos; fees, legal fees and court costs and other expenses related to any &#xA;such activities or any claims in connection therewith.  To the extent &#xA;permitted by law, by entering into this License Agreement, Licensee hereby &#xA;expressly consents to (i) Licensor sending information to Licensee from time &#xA;to time advertising the various products that Licensor provides, whether or &#xA;not such products are provided under this License Agreement; (ii) the use of &#xA;Licensee&apos;s name in Licensor customer lists, promotional materials and/or &#xA;press releases; and (iii) the collection and use by Licensor of information &#xA;about the computer system on which the Licensed Software is installed (e.g. &#xA;product version, serial number) for  internal security and licensing &#xA;purposes; Licensor does not use this information to identify individuals &#xA;utilizing such software.&#xA;17 MISCELLANEOUS. Licensor may assign this License &#xA;Agreement to any member of Licensor&apos;s group of companies or to a purchaser of &#xA;the intellectual property rights in the Licensed Software, but otherwise &#xA;neither this License Agreement nor any rights hereunder may be assigned (any &#xA;change of control merger, sale or other transfer of all, or substantially &#xA;all, of the assets of Licensee shall be included in the meaning of an &#xA;assignment) nor duties delegated by either party, and any attempt to do so &#xA;will be void.  If Licensee acquires the Licensed Software in North America, &#xA;the laws of the state of Maryland govern this License Agreement and it shall &#xA;be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the State of &#xA;Maryland.  If Licensee acquires the Licensed Software in France, Germany or &#xA;Japan, this License Agreement is governed by the laws of the country in which &#xA;Licensee acquired the Licensed Software.  In the rest of the world the laws &#xA;of England govern this License Agreement.  The aforesaid applicable law shall &#xA;apply without regard to conflicts of laws provisions thereof, and without &#xA;regard to the United Nations Convention on the International Sale of Goods.  &#xA;Other than for North American transactions, this License Agreement shall be &#xA;subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the country &#xA;determining the applicable law as aforesaid.  This License Agreement is in &#xA;addition expressly made subject to any United States, United Kingdom or &#xA;European Union laws, regulations and other restrictions regarding export or &#xA;re-export of computer software and technology.  Licensee agrees not to export &#xA;or re-export any Licensed Software or derivative thereof in contradiction to &#xA;any such applicable restriction.  Except for the Product Order, this License &#xA;Agreement is the complete and exclusive statement of agreement between the &#xA;parties relating to the license for the Licensed Software and supersedes all &#xA;proposals, communications, purchase orders, and prior agreements, verbal or &#xA;written, including without limitation prior end user license agreements in &#xA;relation to the Licensed Software between the parties and end user license &#xA;agreements embedded in such Licensed Software.  Upon Licensee&apos;s properly &#xA;authorized installation of any update and/or upgrade of any Licensed Software &#xA;licensed hereunder, the license granted to such prior version and/or release &#xA;shall terminate after a ninety (90) day transition period from such &#xA;installation and only the license to such updated and/or upgraded Licensed &#xA;Software shall continue.  No employee, agent, or representative of Licensor &#xA;has the authority to bind Licensor to any oral representation or warranty &#xA;concerning the Licensed Software.  No representation or statement not &#xA;expressly contained in this License Agreement nor any supplement, &#xA;modification, or amendment of this License Agreement will be binding on &#xA;either party unless executed in writing by a duly authorized representative &#xA;of each party to this License Agreement.  &#xA;ANNEX 1&#xA;A. LICENSE OPTIONS FOR THE FOLLOWING SOFTWARE PRODUCTS:&#xA;CaliberRMTM, TeamDefineTM, Together®, StarTeam®, TempoTM, TeamDemand®, &#xA;TeamFocusTM, TeamInspectorTM, SilkCentral®, Test ManagerTM, SilkTest®, &#xA;Silk4JTM, SilkPerformer® including portions thereof, other products within &#xA;the same product families and other Software Products where indicated by &#xA;Licensor.&#xA;&#xA;Regardless of the type of license, each copy of the Licensed Software &#xA;contains (i) software that provides services on a computer called a server &#xA;(&apos;Server Software&apos;) and (ii) software that allows a computer or &#xA;workstation to access or utilize the services provided by the Server Software &#xA;(&apos;Client Software&apos;). For any type of license acquired, Licensee may &#xA;install one copy of the Server Software on a single computer (the computer &#xA;running the Server Software shall be referred to as the &apos;Server&apos;). &#xA;The number of Client Software copies that may be installed is determined by &#xA;the type of license acquired as set forth below.&#xA;&#xA;1. Named User A Named User license means Licensee may &#xA;allow only one (1) designated person in Licensee&apos;s organization (&apos;Named &#xA;User&apos;) to use the Licensed Software per Named User license purchased &#xA;(each, a &apos;Named User License&apos;). The foregoing Named User Licenses &#xA;shall be for access and use, only by the equivalent number of Named Users &#xA;licenses purchased. For each Named User, Licensee may install the Client &#xA;Software on up to five (5) computers provided that the Named User is the only &#xA;individual permitted to use the Licensed Software.&#xA;&#xA;2. Concurrent User A Concurrent User License means &#xA;Licensee may install the Client Software on a reasonable number of computers &#xA;or machines, provided that the Licensed Software is used only by as many &#xA;concurrent users at any given moment in time as Licensee has purchased &#xA;concurrent licenses and provided further that Licensee&apos;s use of the Licensed &#xA;Software (both Client Software and Server Software) is only on computers or &#xA;machines located in the Territory and accessed only by users physically &#xA;located in the Territory. The foregoing license shall be for access and use, &#xA;only by the equivalent number of concurrent users for whom Licensee has paid &#xA;the applicable license fees. As used in this Section, use or in use means &#xA;that the Licensed Software is &quot;in use&quot; on a computer or machine when it is &#xA;loaded into random access memory (RAM) of that computer and &#xA;&apos;access&apos; means the ability to use, copy or operate the Licensed &#xA;Software . The Licensed Software may not be shared or used concurrently on &#xA;computers or machines located outside of the Territory or in such a way to &#xA;enable use or access by users located outside the Territory.  &apos;Territory&apos; &#xA;means the geographical area in which the Licensed Software may be used. The &#xA;use in the Territory shall be subject to applicable export restrictions. &#xA;Territory may be any one, and only one, of the following three geographic &#xA;areas: Americas Territory, EMEA Territory or AsiaPac Territory each as &#xA;defined below. The Territory shall be based on the primary business location &#xA;of the Licensor, unless otherwise specified in a Product Order. The &#xA;geographic Territories are: (i) &apos;Americas Territory&apos; including and limited to &#xA;those geographical areas found within the boundaries of North and South &#xA;America. (ii) &apos;Europe, Middle East and Africa Territory&apos; or &apos;EMEA Territory&apos; &#xA;including and limited to those geographical areas found within the boundaries &#xA;of Europe, Middle East and Africa, including all the countries which are part &#xA;of the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Jersey, Guernsey, Isle of Man, &#xA;Iceland, Monaco, Andorra, Liechtenstein, San Marino, Albania, all the &#xA;countries of the former Yugoslavia, Israel, Turkey, countries of the Arab &#xA;Middle East,  all the countries of the former Soviet Union, Africa, &#xA;Madagascar, and the Islands of the South Indian Ocean. (iii) &apos;Asia Pacific &#xA;Territory&apos; or &apos;AsiaPac Territory&apos; including and limited to those geographical &#xA;areas found within the boundaries of Asia and Australia/Pacific including &#xA;South Korea, Japan, China, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau India, Maldives, &#xA;Pakistan, Myanmar, Nepal, Bhutan, Bangladesh, Thailand, Laos, Cambodia, &#xA;Vietnam, Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, East Timor, the Philippines, Brunei, &#xA;Papua New Guinea, the Pacific Ocean Islands, Australia, and New Zealand.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;3.  Virtual User (SilkPerformer only) A &quot;Virtual User&quot; &#xA;represents a simulation of a particular individual user executing a &#xA;transaction or sequence of operations. Virtual Users are further qualified by &#xA;class, and may be licensed on either a Node-Locked or Concurrent User basis. &#xA;If a Virtual User is licensed on a Node-Locked basis (as provided below) &#xA;(&apos;Node-Locked Virtual User License&apos;), that Virtual User may be &#xA;associated with a Multi-Machine Controller (&apos;MMC&apos;) component of the &#xA;Licensed Software only on the particular system for which the Virtual User is &#xA;licensed. If a Virtual User is licensed on a Concurrent User basis (as &#xA;provided below) (&apos;Concurrent Virtual User License&apos;), then that &#xA;Virtual User may be associated with any licensed instantiation of a MMC at &#xA;any one time, but during the operation of that instantiation, may not be &#xA;associated with any other instantiation of a MMC at the same time. By way of &#xA;example; if 50 Virtual Users are licensed on a Concurrent User basis, &#xA;Licensee may simultaneously associate all 50 with one MMC instantiation; or &#xA;simultaneously may associate 20 with one MMC instantiation and 30 with a &#xA;second MMC instantiation; but could not, for example, simultaneously &#xA;associate 30 with each of the two MMC instantiations. A &quot;Web Virtual User&quot; is &#xA;a Virtual User limited to performing actions in basic web-based applications &#xA;making use of the common web protocols set forth in the accompanying release &#xA;notes. A &quot;Standard Virtual User&quot; is a Virtual User that has all of the rights &#xA;of a Web Virtual User, and that may additionally make use of certain client-&#xA;server, database and other protocols as set forth in the accompanying release &#xA;notes. A &quot;Premium Virtual User&quot; is a Virtual User that has all of the rights &#xA;of a Standard Virtual User, and that may additionally make use of certain &#xA;protocols for packaged third-party applications and complex enterprise &#xA;technologies as set forth in the accompanying release notes.  Node-Locked &#xA;Virtual User Licenses and Concurrent Virtual User Licenses are available for &#xA;the MMC or Service Analysis Module (&apos;SAM&apos;) component of the &#xA;Licensed Software. A Node Locked Virtual User License means Licensee may use &#xA;the Licensed Software in object code form on a production basis on one (1) &#xA;computer and to permit the Licensed Software to be used and accessed at any &#xA;one time by no more than the number of users indicated in the applicable &#xA;Product Order (each a &quot;Node Locked User&quot;). If no number is indicated, the &#xA;number shall be 1.  A Concurrent Virtual User License means the same as the &#xA;Concurrent User license option above.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Notes(i) Multiplexing software:  The use of one or more &#xA;external tools, including multiplexors or replicators, to reduce the number &#xA;of users directly connected to the Licensed Software shall not exempt &#xA;Licensee from acquiring licenses for all users. For example, use of &#xA;multiplexing or connection pooling software or hardware to reduce the number &#xA;of users directly connected to the Licensed Software, the number of Named &#xA;Users or Concurrent Users within Licensee&apos;s organization using the Licensed &#xA;Software shall be measured as the number of distinct inputs to the &#xA;multiplexing or connection pooling front end and Licensee shall purchase the &#xA;equivalent number of Named User or Concurrent User Licenses. If Licensee uses &#xA;replicator software, Licensee may not use the Licensed Software or share &#xA;licenses in any way not explicitly provided for in this License Agreement.  &#xA;(ii) APIs: Any user of any third party application that &#xA;calls any Licensed Software application programming interfaces (&apos;Product &#xA;APIs&apos;) must have a valid license to connect to the Licensed Software. &#xA;Licensee shall not, and shall not allow others, to reverse engineer, &#xA;decompile, or disassemble the Product APIs. Commercial distribution of any &#xA;products that include Product APIs requires a separate distribution license &#xA;and such license is not granted by this License Agreement.  (iii) &#xA;TeamInspector:  TeamInspector is licensed on a Named User basis &#xA;only.  &#xA;B. LICENSE OPTIONS FOR THE FOLLOWING SOFTWARE &#xA;PRODUCTS:&#xA;&#xA;All Application Middleware products including AppServerTM and VisiBroker® &#xA;including portions thereof, other products within the same product families &#xA;and other Software Products where indicated by Licensor.&#xA;1. Development License Options&#xA;(a) Named User: For each Named User License, Licensee may &#xA;install and execute the Licensed Software on one (1) computer for use by one &#xA;(1) person in Licensee&apos;s organization solely to develop, compile (including &#xA;byte code compile), and test, in source or object code form, Licensee&apos;s own &#xA;application programs and other works (&quot;Works&quot;) designed to work with the &#xA;Licensed Software. Unless Licensee has purchased a valid Deployment License &#xA;as described below, Licensee may not deploy or use the Licensed Software on a &#xA;production basis. The Licensed Software contains certain time-out features &#xA;designed to prevent the Licensed Software from being deployed in a runtime &#xA;environment for longer than a specified period without Deployment License &#xA;keys. Deployment License keys will be provided to Licensee at such time as &#xA;Licensee purchases the requisite Deployment Licenses.  WORKS CREATED USING &#xA;THE LICENSED SOFTWARE MAY REQUIRE THE LICENSED SOFTWARE IN ORDER TO RUN. &#xA;WITHOUT THE REQUISITE DEPLOYMENT LICENSE KEYS, THE LICENSED SOFTWARE WILL BE &#xA;DISABLED AND THOSE WORKS MAY NO LONGER RUN. LICENSEE SHOULD THEREFORE TAKE &#xA;PRECAUTIONS TO AVOID ANY LOSS OF DATA THAT MIGHT RESULT.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;2. Deployment License Options&#xA;(a) Concurrent User: For each Concurrent User Deployment &#xA;License, License may install the Licensed Software, in executable form only, &#xA;on a server accessed and used by multiple users over a network, provided that &#xA;the Licensed Software is used only by as many concurrent users at any given &#xA;moment in time as Licensee has purchased concurrent licenses and provided &#xA;further that use of the Licensed Software is only in the Territory and &#xA;accessed only by users physically located in the Territory. The foregoing &#xA;license shall be for access and use, only by the equivalent number of &#xA;concurrent users for whom Licensee has paid the applicable license fees, &#xA;solely to create, compile (including byte code compile), test and deploy, in &#xA;source or object code form, Works. As used in this Section, use or in use &#xA;means that the Licensed Software is &quot;in use&quot; on a computer or machine when it &#xA;is loaded into random access memory (RAM) of that computer. The Licensed &#xA;Software may not be shared or used concurrently on computers or machines &#xA;located outside of the Territory or in such a way to enable use or access by &#xA;users located outside the Territory.&#xA;&#xA;(b) Server/CPU: For each Server/CPU Deployment License &#xA;Licensee may install and execute the Licensed Software in object code form on &#xA;a production basis on one (1) server hardware unit that is operating the &#xA;platform designated in the applicable Product Order and that has no more than &#xA;the number of CPUs designated in the applicable Product Order and to permit &#xA;the Licensed Software as so installed to be accessed at any one time by an &#xA;unlimited number of concurrent users. Licensee may not install or execute the &#xA;Licensed Software on any type of device that has a greater number of CPUs and &#xA;Licensee may not, under a given Server/CPU Deployment License, install or &#xA;execute the Licensed Software on more than one (1) computer. Licensee may use &#xA;and deploy the Licensed Software either as a Server or as a Client. Use of &#xA;the Licensed Software as a &quot;Server&quot; means to manage and control the automated &#xA;exchanges of information with one or more remote computers through various &#xA;telecommunications channels. Use of the Licensed Software as a &quot;Client&quot; means &#xA;to operate the Licensed Software on a computer to facilitate communications &#xA;with the Server. The Client shall not act as or perform the functions of a &#xA;Server.  A Client may make only a maximum of 10 concurrent call backs. A &#xA;Client shall not have POA (Portable Object Adapter) policies with the &#xA;following values:  &#xA;LifespanPolicyValue.PERSISTENT; &#xA;RequestProcessingPolicyValue.USE_SERVANT_MANAGER;&#xA;RequestProcessingPolicyValue.USE_DEFAULT_SERVANT&#xA;Subject to these restrictions and limitations and any additional &#xA;restrictions or limitations that may appear in the applicable Product Order, &#xA;Licensee may install the Client on an unlimited number of computers. Licensee &#xA;receives no right to deploy Clients without the purchase of a Server/CPU &#xA;Deployment License.&#xA;&#xA;(c) Backup Server License Option for AppServer and &#xA;VisiBroker Licensee may install the Licensed Software on a single &#xA;backup server and use the Licensed Software in object code form solely for &#xA;backup or disaster recovery purposes (&apos;Backup Server License&apos;). &#xA;Licensee may not use the Licensed Software on a production basis except &#xA;during periods when one or more copies of the Licensed Software for which &#xA;Licensee has purchased a Deployment License are nonfunctional, and, in such &#xA;event, only in accordance with the terms of the Deployment License.&#xA;&#xA;(d) Standby Server License Option for AppServer and &#xA;VisiBroker Licensee may install the Licensed Software on a single &#xA;standby server and use the Licensed Software in object code form solely in a &#xA;standby, non-production mode for use in the event the primary server fails &#xA;(&apos;Standby Server License&apos;). Licensee may not use the Licensed &#xA;Software on a production basis under a Standby Server License except during &#xA;periods when one or more copies of the Licensed Software for which Licensee &#xA;has purchased a Deployment License are nonfunctional, and, in such event, &#xA;only in accordance with the terms of the Deployment License.&#xA;&#xA;C. OTHER LICENSE OPTIONS &#xA;1. System Partitioning /LPAR/IFL Licensed Software may be &#xA;licensed for installation and use on computer systems which incorporate &#xA;logical partitioning (LPAR), and/or Integrated Facility for Linux &#xA;(&apos;IFL&apos;) provided such rights have been expressly granted to &#xA;Licensee by Licensor in writing and Licensee complies with the restrictions &#xA;set forth in this Section.  The licensing models in this Section 1 are only &#xA;applicable to Server type licenses and are not available for computer systems &#xA;where system resources (e.g. Cores/CPUs) may be scaled down or varied (e.g. &#xA;&apos;Pay Per Use&apos; or &apos;Pay Per Forecast&apos; models).&#xA;(a)  Logical Partitioning (LPAR):  The licensing &#xA;requirements of computer systems (e.g. a Host Server) which incorporate hard &#xA;and/or soft partitioning shall have their licensing requirements determined &#xA;as follows: &#xA;(i)  Hard Partitioning:  Hard partitioning is established &#xA;by using a hard physical partition to physically segment a single larger &#xA;server so that the Host Server utilizing the Licensed Software is a separate &#xA;and distinct smaller system (that is, each separate system acts as a &#xA;physically independent, self-contained server with its own CPUs, operating &#xA;system, separate boot area, memory, input/output subsystem and network &#xA;resources).  Examples of such hard partitioning include: Dynamic System &#xA;Domains (DSD) -- enabled by Dynamic Reconfiguration (DR), Solaris 10 &#xA;Containers (capped Containers only), LPAR (adds DLPAR with AIX 5.2), Micro-&#xA;Partitions (capped partitions only), vPar, nPar, Integrity Virtual Machine &#xA;(capped partitions only), Secure Resource Partitions (capped partitions &#xA;only), and Static Hard Partitioning.  For computer systems where hard &#xA;partitioning has been employed to create the Host Server being utilized to &#xA;operate the Licensed Software, such Host Server shall be licensed pursuant to &#xA;the terms and conditions set forth in this Section 1 as if such Host Server &#xA;where a separate and distinct computer system.  For example, where the total &#xA;computer system has 8 Cores/CPUs but only 4 Cores/CPUs have been hard &#xA;portioned to use the Licensed Software, Licensee shall only be required to &#xA;license such 4 Cores/CPUs on such hard partitioned system. &#xA;(ii)  Soft Partitioning:  Soft partitioning is &#xA;established by using the computer systems operating system resource manager &#xA;to segment and limit the number of Cores/CPUs where the Licensed Software is &#xA;running by creating areas where processor resources are allocated and limited &#xA;within the same operating system.  Examples of such soft partitioning &#xA;include: Solaris 9 Resource Containers, AIX Workload Manager, HP Process &#xA;Resource Manager, Affinity Management, Oracle VM, and VMware.  For computer &#xA;systems where soft partitioning has been employed to create the Host Server &#xA;being utilized to operate the Licensed Software, such Host Server shall be &#xA;licensed pursuant to the terms and conditions set forth in this Section 1 as &#xA;if such Host Server where a separate and distinct computer system but the &#xA;Cores/CPU required to be licensed shall be an &apos;expected&apos; Cores/CPU &#xA;number calculated as the ratio of the number of Cores/CPUs soft partitioned &#xA;as a percentage of the entire computer system&apos; Cores/CPUs, increased by ten &#xA;percent (10%).  For example, on an 8 Core/CPU computer system where soft &#xA;partitioning has been utilized such that only 4 Cores/CPUs are allocated to &#xA;use the Licensed Software, a Server License fee charge equal to 60% of the &#xA;total computer system Cores/CPUs would be required (50%+10% = 60% of an 8 &#xA;Core/CPU system license fee). &#xA;(b)  Integrated Facility for Linux (&apos;IFL&apos;):  An &#xA;Integrated Facility for Linux or IFL Host Server is established by using a &#xA;dedicated Host Server where the IFL Host Server is isolated from general use &#xA;and is only capable of utilizing the Linux operating system and running Linux &#xA;applications and cannot run other operating systems or applications.  For IFL &#xA;Host Server computer systems being utilized to operate the Licensed Software, &#xA;such IFL Host Server shall be licensed pursuant to the terms and conditions &#xA;set forth in this Section 1 as if such IFL Host Server were a separate and &#xA;distinct computer system.  For example, where the total computer system that &#xA;has 8 Cores/CPUs but the IFL Host Server is a 4 Cores/CPUs IFL computer &#xA;system and the IFL system is the only system using the Licensed Software, &#xA;Licensee shall only be required to license such 4 Cores/CPUs on such IFL Host &#xA;Server system. &#xA;(c )&#x9;LPAR and IFL Host Server Verification:  Licensee &#xA;shall provide to Licensor, upon commencement of this License Agreement and at &#xA;such other times as Licensor may reasonably request, confirmation that &#xA;Licensee&apos;s computer systems comply with the LPAR and/or IFL license &#xA;requirements set forth in Subsections 1(a) and (b) above. Such confirmation &#xA;shall be signed by a director or officer of Licensee and shall be accompanied &#xA;by all information as Licensor reasonably requires to verify that Licensee is &#xA;utilizing the Licensed Software in compliance with the terms and conditions &#xA;of the License Agreement. The foregoing is in addition to Licensor&apos;s rights &#xA;under Section 3 of the License Agreement.&#xA;2. Evaluation License Option Licensed Software provided &#xA;under this License Option gives Licensee a term license to use the Licensed &#xA;Software within Licensee&apos;s organization during the evaluation term specified &#xA;in writing by Licensor, solely for evaluation and testing purposes on a &#xA;single computer system and not for development, commercial, or production &#xA;purposes. Licensee may not reproduce or distribute the Licensed Software. &#xA;Licensee&apos;s results of benchmark or other performance tests run on or using &#xA;the Licensed Software may not be disclosed to any third party without &#xA;Licensor&apos;s prior written consent. At any time during the evaluation term or &#xA;upon completion thereof, Licensee may, upon written notification to Licensor &#xA;and payment of the applicable license fee, replace the evaluation license &#xA;with a license to use the Licensed Software pursuant to one of the other &#xA;applicable options listed in Annex1.  In the absence of such notification by &#xA;Licensee, the evaluation license shall automatically terminate at the end of &#xA;the evaluation term and Licensee shall return, or, if Licensor so directs, &#xA;delete and destroy all such Licensed Software and provide Licensor with &#xA;written confirmation of such deletion and destruction being completed. &#xA;Licensor may, in its sole discretion, grant Licensee an extension to the &#xA;evaluation term subject to receiving a written request and reasons for such &#xA;request from Licensee prior to expiration of the evaluation term. Licensor &#xA;will specify any such agreed extension in writing to Licensee. Licensed &#xA;Software provided by Licensor free of license fee charge shall be deemed to &#xA;be provided pursuant to this Evaluation License Option unless otherwise &#xA;agreed in writing. In the absence of any contrary period specified in writing &#xA;by Licensor, the evaluation term shall be deemed to be thirty (30) days. In &#xA;relation to Licensed Software provided pursuant to this Evaluation License &#xA;Option, this Section shall prevail over any contrary provisions set forth in &#xA;this License Agreement unless specifically provided otherwise.&#xA;3. Test License Option Licensed Software provided under &#xA;this License Option gives Licensee a limited license to use the Licensed &#xA;Software solely for Licensee&apos;s internal testing purposes on a single computer &#xA;system. At no time may Licensee use the Licensed Software for development, &#xA;commercial, or production purposes, nor may Licensee reproduce or distribute &#xA;the Licensed Software or any software application programs created with it. &#xA;The applicable license fee for this License Option will be determined by the &#xA;access or use to be tested. For example, batch process testing will require &#xA;the payment of the applicable license fee for a Licensor server license for &#xA;CPU. Licensee&apos;s results of benchmark or other performance tests run on or &#xA;using the Licensed Software may not be disclosed to any third party without &#xA;Licensor&apos;s prior written consent.  If Licensee uses the Test Licenses for any &#xA;purpose other than for Licensee&apos;s internal testing purposes, the Test License &#xA;shall terminate automatically and without notice.  Upon such termination, &#xA;Licensee may convert the terminated Test License to a standard license type &#xA;listed above by paying the applicable conversion fee.  In relation to &#xA;Licensed Software provided pursuant to this Test License Option, this Section &#xA;shall prevail over any contrary provisions set forth in this License &#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;ANNEX 2  SPECIFIC SOFTWARE TERMS&#xA;The following terms and conditions apply to the applicable Licensed &#xA;Software products named below and supersede any conflicting terms and &#xA;conditions set forth elsewhere in this License Agreement:&#xA;ACADEMIC EDITIONS/USER  This Licensed Software may be &#xA;used solely for Licensee&apos;s personal use in providing or receiving instruction &#xA;within the limited scope of guided computer programming and/or software &#xA;training course(s) in which Licensee is a direct and personal participant, &#xA;either as student or instructor (&apos;Course(s)&apos;). The Licensed &#xA;Software may only be used with other participants of the Courses and then &#xA;only for educational or training purposes. The Licensed Software may not be &#xA;used for any commercial, business, governmental or institutional purpose of &#xA;any kind, except to the extent Licensee is an instructor teaching a Course. &#xA;&#xA;SILKCENTRAL, TEST MANAGER, SILKTEST, SILK4J, &#xA;SILKPERFORMER  This Licensed Software may include technology for &#xA;monitoring authorized use, including the policy files and license keys &#xA;required to use the Licensed Software (the &apos;License Authorization &#xA;Server&apos; or &apos;LAS&apos;).  The LAS may be installed on a single-&#xA;specified computer system at the specific site for which Licensee has &#xA;contracted (the &apos;Designated System&apos;). The LAS, or any part thereof, &#xA;may not be transferred from the Designated System. Regardless of the &#xA;installation of the LAS, Licensee must remain compliant with the terms in &#xA;this License Agreement (including without limitation any license restrictions &#xA;and number of users permitted pursuant to this License Agreement).  The LAS &#xA;cannot be used or installed on a Virtual Machine.&#xA;&#xA;SILK PERFORMER. This Licensed Software may be installed &#xA;on a reasonable number of Licensee computer systems. Licensee may use the &#xA;Multi-Machine Controller (also referred to as &apos;Workbench&apos;) &#xA;(&apos;MMC&apos;) component and related load-test agents on an unlimited &#xA;number of machines for an unlimited number of users, but solely in connection &#xA;with the use of SilkPerformer in accordance with the number, type and class &#xA;of Virtual User Licenses purchased.  Premium Virtual User Licenses for &#xA;SilkPerformer, when ordered in any quantity, include a single Named User &#xA;limited license to use SilkTest (the &apos;Additional Product&apos;). The &#xA;Additional Product may be used ONLY in conjunction with the Premium Virtual &#xA;User Licenses of SilkPerformer and may not be used or transferred on a stand-&#xA;alone basis. Incremental use of any Additional Product beyond the single &#xA;Named User license, or stand-alone use, must be licensed and paid for &#xA;separately.&#xA;&#xA;TOGETHER.  This Licensed Software may be used solely to &#xA;create, compile (including byte code compile), test and deploy, in source or &#xA;object code form, Licensee application programs and other works. This &#xA;Licensed Software requires registration with Licensor prior to use. Licensee &#xA;will be prompted to register at the time of installation or first use, at &#xA;which time Licensee will be notified, or directed to online resources &#xA;explaining, how registration information provided by Licensee may be used and &#xA;Licensee will be afforded the opportunity to opt out of certain uses of such &#xA;information. Licensee may use the License Manager component of the Licensed &#xA;Software, in executable form only, on a server for use solely in connection &#xA;with Licensee&apos;s use of the Licensed Software.&#xA;&#xA;TEAMDEFINE. This Licensed Software includes the &#xA;capability for an unlimited number of users to review the simulation program &#xA;integrated into the Licensed Software by Licensor or its suppliers. Such &#xA;users may not otherwise use the Licensed Software.  Where an evaluation &#xA;license option is obtained for this Licensed Software pursuant to Annex 1.C.2 &#xA;the evaluation period will continue for up to 365 days. During the first 30 &#xA;days of the evaluation period Licensee will be able to access all &#xA;functionality of this Licensed Software except &apos;Project Export&apos;. &#xA;During the remaining evaluation period such functionality will continue &#xA;except that Licensee will have read only access to &apos;simulations&apos;, &#xA;&apos;requirements&apos;, &apos;SDK&apos;, &apos;integrations&apos;, &#xA;&apos;images&apos; and &apos;templates&apos;. Licensee may purchase a full &#xA;license for this Licensed Software at any time during the evaluation period. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;SILKCENTRAL, TEST MANAGER, SILKTEST, SILK4J, SILKPERFORMER, &#xA;TEAMDEFINE, CALIBER, TOGETHER, STARTEAM, TEMPO, TEAMDEMAND, TEAMFOCUS, &#xA;TEAMINSPECTOR, APPSERVER, VISIBROKER. This Licensed Software may be &#xA;used in a Virtual Machine only where a concurrent user license has been &#xA;granted&#xA;&#xA;APPSERVER, VISIBROKER. For this Licensed Software, &#xA;regardless of the number of CPU&apos;s for which Licensee has purchased a &#xA;Deployment License: (i) Licensee may not run more than one instance of the &#xA;deployed Licensed Software on a single computer, and (ii) the Licensed &#xA;Software may not be accessed at any one time by more than the number of &#xA;Concurrent Users indicated in the applicable Product Order. In the event &#xA;Licensee desire additional instances or additional Concurrent Users, Licensee &#xA;must purchase a separate license applicable to a different computer.&#xA;&#xA;APPLICATION MIDDLEWARE PRODUCTS.  Licensee may not &#xA;include this Licensed Software or any component thereof in any general-&#xA;purpose software development tool, library, component, or any other product &#xA;that is generally competitive with or a substitute for the Licensed Software &#xA;or any other Licensor product offerings; nor may Licensee use the Licensed &#xA;Software to create a product or operate a service that is generally &#xA;competitive with the Licensed Software or any other Licensor product &#xA;offerings, including any general-purpose software development tool. The &#xA;foregoing restriction does not apply, however, to use of the Licensed &#xA;Software to develop &quot;plug-ins&quot; (i.e., integrations created using the Licensed &#xA;Software&apos;s open tools API) so long as such plug-ins are designed to provide &#xA;supplementary functionality to the Licensed Software.  &#xA;&#xA;This Licensed Software is not redistributable. Licensee is not permitted &#xA;to reproduce the Licensed Software for sublicensing, resale, lending, &#xA;leasing, deployment or distribution to any party, including without &#xA;limitation, distributing the Licensed Software as part of a VAR, OEM, &#xA;distributor or reseller arrangement. If Licensee integrates the Licensed &#xA;Software into a Work and intends to distribute or resell the resulting &#xA;integrated Work, Licensee must contact Licensor to obtain the appropriate &#xA;distribution license.&#xA;&#xA;The portions of this Licensed Software identified as  VISISECURE,  &#xA;VISITRANSACT,  VISINOTIFY,  VISITIME and  VISITELCOLOG (collectively, the &quot; &#xA;VISISERVICES&quot;) are not redistributable. This License Agreement does not &#xA;permit Licensee to execute, or otherwise use the  VISISERVICES portion of the &#xA;Licensed Software for any purpose unless Licensee has acquired a separate &#xA;Development and/or Deployment License for  VISISERVICES directly from &#xA;Licensor before developing or deploying any Work that uses such portion of &#xA;the Licensed Software. Licensee is not permitted to reproduce  VISISERVICES &#xA;for sublicensing, resale, lending, leasing, deployment or distribution to any &#xA;party, including without limitation, distributing VISISERVICES as part of a &#xA;VAR, OEM, distributor or reseller arrangement. If Licensee integrates  &#xA;VISISERVICES into a Work and intends to distribute or resell the resulting &#xA;integrated Work, Licensee must contact Licensor to obtain the appropriate &#xA;distribution license.&#xA;&#xA;Notwithstanding the prohibition hereunder against decompiling this &#xA;Licensed Software, Licensee may use that portion of the Licensed Software &#xA;identified as &quot;API Decompiler&quot; for inspecting the public application &#xA;programming interface (API) of the JAVA BEANS COMPONENT LIBRARY, DATAEXPRESS, &#xA;DBSWING and OPENTOOLS API modules.&#xA;&#xA;The following Java Technology Restrictions are applicable to the component &#xA;of this Licensed Software identified as SonicMQ if it accompanies the &#xA;Licensed Software: Licensee may not modify the Java Platform Interface &#xA;(&quot;JPI&quot;, identified as classes contained within the &quot;java&quot; package or any &#xA;subpackages of the &quot;java&quot; package), by creating additional classes within the &#xA;JPI or otherwise causing the addition to or modification of the classes in &#xA;the JPI. In the event that Licensee otherwise create an additional class and &#xA;associated API(s) which (i) extends the functionality of a Java platform, and &#xA;(ii) is exposed to third party software developers for the purpose of &#xA;developing additional software which invokes such additional API, Licensee &#xA;must promptly publish broadly an accurate specification for such API for free &#xA;use by all developers. Licensee may not create, or authorize its own &#xA;licensees to create additional classes, interfaces, or subpackages that are &#xA;in any way identified as &quot;java&quot;, &quot;javax&quot;, &quot;sun&quot; or similar convention as &#xA;specified by sun in any class file naming convention.&#xA;&#xA;This Licensed Software may include certain files, libraries and/or source &#xA;code specifically designated as &apos;redistributables&apos; by Licensor in &#xA;the accompanying printed or on-line documentation and that are necessary to &#xA;use works created using the Product (&quot;Redistributables&quot;). From time to time, &#xA;Licensor may designate other files as Redistributables. Subject to the terms &#xA;and conditions of this License Agreement, Licensee may freely redistribute &#xA;source code or compiled code that is entirely Licensee&apos;s own and does not &#xA;contain any Redistributables. Subject to the terms and conditions of this &#xA;License Agreement, Licensor grants Licensee the personal, non-exclusive, non-&#xA;transferable and limited license to: (a) make exact copies of the &#xA;Redistributables and distribute those copies solely as components of &#xA;Licensee&apos;s Works and solely as required for permitting end users of the Works &#xA;(&apos;End users&quot;) to install and execute the Works; (b) install and execute &#xA;Redistributables, without modification, solely for Licensee&apos;s own internal &#xA;use; and (c) sublicense to End Users the personal, non-exclusive, non-&#xA;transferable right to install and execute Redistributables, without &#xA;modification, solely as components of Works and solely for such End Users&apos; &#xA;own internal use, subject to End Users&apos; compliance with the restrictions in &#xA;this License Agreement. These rights granted may not be exercised by others, &#xA;including co-developers, regardless of how Licensee&apos;s Works are compiled, &#xA;linked, or packaged. These rights apply only to Redistributables and to no &#xA;other file, library, source code or other component or derivative work of the &#xA;Licensed Software. They may be exercised only with respect to works created &#xA;by Licensee using a duly licensed, properly registered copy of the Licensed &#xA;Software.&#xA;'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam_3.5.feature.jar' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='com.borland.starteam_3.5' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='com.borland.starteam_3.5' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='http://altd.borland.com/update/eclipse3.5/site.xml.Team' version='0.0.0.20180726125020'>
      <properties size='3'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Team'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='Borland&apos;s Eclipse Features for Lifecycle Management.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.category' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='http://altd.borland.com/update/eclipse3.5/site.xml.Team' version='0.0.0.20180726125020'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='1'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam_3.5.feature.group' range='[11.0.0.97v20111028-1643,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643]'>
          <filter>
            (&amp;(|(osgi.os=linux)(osgi.os=solaris)(osgi.os=win32)(osgi.os=macosx))(|(osgi.ws=gtk)(osgi.ws=motif)(osgi.ws=win32)(osgi.ws=carbon))(|(osgi.arch=sparc)(osgi.arch=x86)(osgi.arch=x86_64)))
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.borland.team.starteam.doc.user' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.borland.team.starteam.doc.user' range='[0.0.0,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.team.starteam.doc.user' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.borland.team.starteam.doc.user' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.borland.team.starteam.doc.user' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='2'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.borland.team.starteam.doc.user&#xA;Bundle-Version: 11.0.0.97v20111028-1643&#xA;Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.borland.team.starteam.provider.ui' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.borland.team.starteam.provider.ui' range='[0.0.0,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.team.starteam.provider.ui' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.borland.team.starteam.provider.ui' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.borland.team.starteam.provider.ui' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.borland.team.starteam.provider.ui&#xA;Bundle-Version: 11.0.0.97v20111028-1643&#xA;Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.borland.starteam.gui' version='11.0.0.81' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.borland.starteam.gui' range='[0.0.0,11.0.0.81)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam.gui' version='11.0.0.81'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.borland.starteam.gui' version='11.0.0.81'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.borland.starteam.gui' version='11.0.0.81'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='2'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.borland.starteam.gui&#xA;Bundle-Version: 11.0.0.81&#xA;Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.borland.starteam_3.5.feature.group' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.borland.starteam_3.5.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='8'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%label'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='Borland Software Corporation'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='df_LT.label' value='StarTeam 2009 R2 Eclipse 3.5 Client'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright© 1998-2010 Borland Software Corporation. All rights reserved. All patents pending.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='StarTeam team provider, including StarTeam SDK plug-in.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='Borland StarTeam 2009 R2 End User License Agreement&#xA;IMPORTANT: LICENSOR IS PROVIDING THIS SOFTWARE FOR YOUR USE SUBJECT TO &#xA;YOUR AGREEMENT TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW.  IF &#xA;YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT BY CLICKING ON SETUP&apos;S ACCEPT &#xA;BUTTON, YOU WILL NOT BE ABLE TO USE THE SOFTWARE.  BY CLICKING SETUP&apos;S ACCEPT &#xA;BUTTON YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THIS AGREEMENT, UNDERSTOOD IT, AND &#xA;AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ITS TERMS AND CONDITIONS.&#xA;END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;WHEREAS, Licensor desires to grant to Licensee, and Licensee desires to &#xA;accept from Licensor, a license to use Licensed Software (as defined herein) &#xA;upon the terms and conditions hereinafter set forth; NOW, THEREFORE, Licensor &#xA;and Licensee agree as follows:&#xA;For this End User License Agreement (&apos;License &#xA;Agreement&apos;) the following terms shall have the meanings given &#xA;below:&#xA;&apos;Blades&apos; means multiple server modules housed &#xA;in a single chassis each with its own CPU, hard disk and memory.  &#xA;&apos;Core&apos; means a single unit of processing within &#xA;a computer chip, comprising an arithmetic logic unit, registers, instruction &#xA;fetcher and data fetcher/storer. &apos;CPU&apos; (Central Processor Unit) &#xA;means a data processing unit, normally identified with a single microchip &#xA;mounted on a single circuit board and can comprise several Cores. A computer &#xA;&apos;box&apos; can contain several CPUs. The &apos;box&apos; is sometimes &#xA;referred to as a &apos;server&apos; or a &apos;machine&apos; (or possibly a &#xA;&apos;mainframe&apos;).&#xA;&apos;Licensor&apos; means the Licensor identified in the &#xA;printed End User License Agreement which is (i) included with and/or &#xA;accompanies the program package incorporating this Licensed Software &#xA;delivered to Licensee or (ii) attached to and/or supplied with the electronic &#xA;program download incorporating this Licensed Software delivered to Licensee, &#xA;as appropriate.&#xA;&apos;Licensed Software&apos; means the object code &#xA;version of the Licensor computer programs, their accompanying user &#xA;documentation (&apos;Documentation&apos;) and other supplemental materials as &#xA;provided to Licensee by Licensor, including but not limited to any software &#xA;security keys, modifications or additions relating thereto. The Licensed &#xA;Software shall also include any new releases, updates, revisions, &#xA;modifications, additions, corrections and fixes of the Licensed Software that &#xA;Licensee receives under Sections 6 and 7 below or under maintenance for which &#xA;Licensee has separately contracted and paid. From commencement of this &#xA;License Agreement, the &apos;Licensed Software&apos; shall also include, and &#xA;this License Agreement shall apply to, any prior versions of the Licensed &#xA;Software licensed by Licensee. This License Agreement does not grant Licensee &#xA;the right to any new releases, updates, revisions, modifications, additions, &#xA;corrections and fixes of the Licensed Software unless provided by Licensor &#xA;under Section 6 below. Licensed Software products are available to operate on &#xA;the Windows, Linux, Unix or other computer platforms and a separate license &#xA;is required for a Licensed Software product for each computer platform.&#xA;&apos;Product Order&apos; means a document that has been &#xA;(i) executed by Licensee, describing each Licensed Software license purchased &#xA;and (ii) accepted by Licensor or its authorized distributors.  Licensor will &#xA;accept the Product Order by either confirming Licensor&apos;s acceptance in &#xA;writing or by delivering the Licensed Software Licensee, whichever occurs &#xA;first.  Each Product Order shall constitute a separate agreement and shall &#xA;incorporate therein all of the terms and conditions of this License &#xA;Agreement.  In the event of any conflict between the terms of this License &#xA;Agreement and the terms of any Product Order which have been expressly &#xA;accepted by a duly authorized signatory of Licensor in writing, such terms of &#xA;the Product Order shall govern.  In no event shall any terms and conditions &#xA;of Licensee contained in a purchase order or similar document issued by &#xA;Licensee in connection with this License Agreement or a Product Order apply &#xA;and any such document issued shall be only for the administrative purposes of &#xA;identifying the Licensed Software ordered, the number of licenses, and the &#xA;price to be paid and shall have no other legal effect.&#xA;&apos;Disaster Recovery System&apos; is defined as a &#xA;computer system that is used (i) if a disaster arises and the original &#xA;production system is unavailable, (ii) for the purposes of disaster recovery &#xA;testing and/or (iii) for system diagnostics or maintenance of the Disaster &#xA;Recovery System itself. A Disaster Recovery System does not include any &#xA;system that is in the same computer cluster as the machine on which the &#xA;development or production copy of the Licensed Software is installed.&#xA;&apos;Virtual Machine&apos; means a software &#xA;implementation that executes programs like a physical machine where the &#xA;software running inside the virtual machine is limited to the resources and &#xA;abstractions provided by the virtual machine. &#xA;1 GRANT OF LICENSE.  For payment of the applicable non-&#xA;refundable license fees identified on the Product Order, Licensor grants &#xA;solely to Licensee, as an end user, a personal, perpetual, non-transferable, &#xA;non-sublicensable and non-exclusive license to use the Licensed Software &#xA;subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this License Agreement.  &#xA;Licensee shall have the right to use the Licensed Software solely for its own &#xA;internal use and benefit. For the avoidance of doubt, the license granted &#xA;herein does not permit (i) third party contractors (including without &#xA;limitation outsourcers) to access or use the Licensed Software for Licensee&apos;s &#xA;internal use and benefit without the prior written consent of Licensor and &#xA;the payment of an additional license fee, (ii) the public to access or use &#xA;the Licensed Software (including without limitation, via the internet) except &#xA;as specifically provided in Annex 1 hereunder, and/or (iii) installation, use &#xA;or access of the Licensed Software on, in, or from a Virtual Machine except &#xA;as specifically provided in Annex 1 or Annex 2 hereunder.  Where permitted by &#xA;Licensor pursuant to sections 1(i) and (ii) hereof, Licensee shall be liable &#xA;to Licensor in respect of any breach of this License Agreement resulting from &#xA;any access or use by third party contractors and/or the public.  Access &#xA;and/or use of data, results and/or output obtained and/or generated, either &#xA;directly or indirectly, through the use of any Licensed Software are deemed &#xA;to be access and/or use of such Licensed Software and such data, results &#xA;and/or output shall be subject to the licensing terms and restrictions &#xA;applicable to such Licensed Software.  Different license options are &#xA;available from Licensor as set forth or referred to in Annex 1 (&apos;License &#xA;Option(s)&apos;), although not all License Options are available for each &#xA;specific Licensed Software product. The applicable License Option to be &#xA;purchased by Licensee for the Licensed Software shall be identified in the &#xA;Product Order. Additional License Options (as appropriate) are required to be &#xA;purchased by Licensee for use of the Licensed Software on a Disaster Recovery &#xA;System or for load-balancing, fail-over, training, or testing purposes.  &#xA;Licensed Software purchased for testing purposes will be subject to the Test &#xA;License Option terms and restrictions set forth in Annex 1.C.  Certain &#xA;Licensed Software may also be subject to additional terms and conditions as &#xA;set forth in the &apos;Specific Software Terms&apos; located in Annex 2. The &#xA;Specific Software Terms will prevail in the event of any conflict. &#xA;2 USER RESTRICTION.  Licensee agrees not to:&#xA;2.1&#x9;Copy and distribute the Licensed Software, in whole or in part, &#xA;for internal use without paying Licensor the applicable additional fees, &#xA;except (i) for making a reasonable number of archival back-up copies; or (ii) &#xA;as expressly authorized by Licensor in writing; or (iii) for making a &#xA;reasonable number of copies of the Documentation supplied to Licensee by &#xA;Licensor in electronic form.  Licensee shall reproduce and affix all &#xA;copyright and other proprietary rights notices appearing in or on the &#xA;Licensed Software, including the notices of all third party suppliers and all &#xA;those included in any Third Party Software, as defined below in all such &#xA;copies thereof.&#xA;2.2&#x9;Copy and/or distribute the Licensed Software, in whole or in &#xA;part, to third parties without first entering into a separate distribution &#xA;license agreement with Licensor or permit use or access to all or part of the &#xA;Licensed Software to any third party except as specifically provided in Annex &#xA;1 hereunder. For the avoidance of doubt, third party(ies) include without &#xA;limitation contractors, outsourcers, Licensee&apos;s customers and the public.&#xA;2.3&#x9;Transfer, ship or use the Licensed Software outside the continent &#xA;in which it was originally licensed to Licensee, except as otherwise &#xA;specified in Annex 1 and/or Annex 2.&#xA;2.4&#x9;Install, access or use the Licensed Software on an operating &#xA;system other than the operating system for which the Licensed Software was &#xA;originally licensed to Licensee, except as otherwise specified in Annex 1 &#xA;and/or Annex 2.&#xA;2.5&#x9;Assign, sell, rent, lease, lend, sublicense, outsource or &#xA;otherwise transfer the Licensed Software to any third party, or authorize or &#xA;appoint any third party to do so.&#xA;2.6&#x9;Use the Licensed Software for timesharing, facilities management, &#xA;outsourcing, hosting, service bureau use, other data processing services to &#xA;third parties or like purposes.&#xA;2.7&#x9;Modify the Licensed Software or provide any person with the means &#xA;to do the same. &#xA;2.8&#x9;Create derivative works, translate, disassemble, recompile or &#xA;reverse engineer any Licensed Software or attempt to do so (except to the &#xA;extent applicable law specifically permits such activity).&#xA;2.9&#x9;Alter, destroy, or otherwise remove any proprietary notices or &#xA;labels on or embedded within the Licensed Software or Documentation.&#xA;2.10&#x9;Utilize for itself, or permit any third party to utilize, any &#xA;software application program created, in whole or in part, utilizing any &#xA;Licensed Software without a valid and properly granted Deployment Product &#xA;License.&#xA;2.11&#x9;Use the Licensed Software in a manner other than as specifically &#xA;permitted in this License Agreement.&#xA;3 AUDITS.  Licensee agrees to (i) keep records of and &#xA;provide the location, model and serial number of any and all machines on &#xA;which the Licensed Software is installed or from which the Licensed Software &#xA;is accessed, and the names of and how many users are accessing the Licensed &#xA;Software, (ii) implement a reasonable mechanism or process to ensure that &#xA;Licensee&apos;s use of the Licensed Software does not exceed the number of &#xA;licenses granted, (iii) take all necessary steps to destroy or erase all &#xA;Licensed Software codes, programs and other proprietary information before &#xA;disposing of any media containing the Licensed Software, and (iv) promptly &#xA;provide written notice to Licensor if Licensee&apos;s usage exceeds the license &#xA;granted.  Upon Licensor&apos;s reasonable request, but not more frequently than &#xA;annually without reasonable cause, Licensee shall furnish Licensor with a &#xA;statement signed by a director and/or auditor, as required by Licensor, &#xA;verifying the above and shall permit Licensor to audit the use of the &#xA;Licensed Software at such times as may be mutually agreed upon.  In the event &#xA;Licensee&apos;s usage exceeds the license granted, without prejudice to any other &#xA;rights or remedies Licensor may have, including without limitation injunctive &#xA;relief, Licensee agrees to pay Licensor the then current license and &#xA;maintenance fees for the use of the additional licenses.  Further, if such &#xA;usage exceeds the license granted by more than five percent (5%), Licensee &#xA;shall also reimburse Licensor for the reasonable cost of such audit in &#xA;addition to other amounts due.&#xA;4 DOCUMENTATION.  One (1) electronic copy of Licensor&apos;s &#xA;standard Documentation, describing Licensor&apos;s recommended use and application &#xA;of the Licensed Software, will be furnished free of additional charge to &#xA;Licensee by Licensor with the Licensed Software.  Printed copies of any &#xA;documentation may be available for purchase from Licensor or its authorized &#xA;distributors.&#xA;5 TERM OF LICENSE.  This License Agreement and Licensee&apos;s &#xA;license for the Licensed Software is perpetual, unless a subscription/term &#xA;license has been purchased by Licensee, and is subject to earlier termination &#xA;as provided in this Section 5.  Licensor may terminate this License Agreement &#xA;and Licensee&apos;s license to the Licensed Software immediately by giving &#xA;Licensee written notice of termination in the event that either (i) Licensee &#xA;breaches any term or condition of this License Agreement and Licensee has &#xA;failed to remedy such breach within ten (10) days of the date of notice from &#xA;Licensor to Licensee or (ii) Licensee is wound up,  has a receiver appointed &#xA;or enters into liquidation or bankruptcy or analogous process or processes in &#xA;Licensee&apos;s home country.  Termination shall be without prejudice to any other &#xA;rights or remedies Licensor may have.  Licensee may at any time terminate &#xA;this License Agreement voluntarily by giving written notice of termination to &#xA;Licensor.  In the event of any termination Licensee will have no right to &#xA;keep or use the Licensed Software or any copy of the Licensed Software for &#xA;any purpose and Licensee shall destroy and erase all copies of such Licensed &#xA;Software in its possession or control, and forward written certification to &#xA;Licensor that all such copies of Licensed Software have been destroyed or &#xA;erased.  &#xA;6 MAINTENANCE.  Where Licensee purchases maintenance &#xA;services, Licensee&apos;s initial maintenance term will begin upon delivery to &#xA;Licensee of the Licensed Software and continue for one (1) year thereafter &#xA;unless otherwise specified in the applicable annual maintenance agreement or &#xA;in the Product Order, or earlier if the license is terminated.  Where &#xA;Licensee purchases maintenance for any Licensed Software product licensed &#xA;hereunder, Licensee hereby agrees that it shall purchase such support &#xA;services for all of Licensee&apos;s licensed copies of such Licensed Software &#xA;product on the relevant computer platform.  Maintenance services provided by &#xA;Licensor will be subject to Licensor&apos;s then current applicable annual &#xA;maintenance agreement unless otherwise agreed by the parties in writing.  &#xA;7 LIMITED WARRANTY.  Licensor warrants for a period of &#xA;ninety (90) days from delivery to Licensee (&apos;Warranty Period&apos;) (i) &#xA;that the media on which the Licensed Software is supplied is free from &#xA;defects in materials or workmanship under normal use and (ii) that the copy &#xA;of the Licensed Software delivered to Licensee conforms in all material &#xA;respects to the Documentation.  As the sole and exclusive remedy for not &#xA;meeting part (i) of the above warranty, Licensor&apos;s sole obligation shall be &#xA;to repair or replace free of charge any defective media on which the Licensed &#xA;Software is delivered if the media is returned to Licensor by Licensee during &#xA;the Warranty Period.  As the sole and exclusive remedy for not meeting part &#xA;(ii) of the above warranty, Licensor shall repair or replace the Licensed &#xA;Software free of charge or if Licensor reasonably determines that such remedy &#xA;is not economically or technically feasible, Licensee shall be entitled to a &#xA;full refund of the license fee and any maintenance fee paid by Licensee with &#xA;respect to that particular Licensed Software and Licensee&apos;s license to use &#xA;such Licensed Software will terminate.  The warranty set forth in this &#xA;Section 7 shall not apply if the defect in the Licensed Software is the &#xA;result of: (a) the Licensed Software not being used in accordance with the &#xA;Documentation, this License Agreement or with the platform(s) for which the &#xA;Licensed Software has been designed and licensed by Licensor; or (b) the &#xA;Licensed Software having been altered, modified or converted by Licensee or &#xA;any third party except as may be specified in the Documentation; or (c) the &#xA;malfunctioning of Licensee&apos;s equipment; or (d) accident or abuse; or (e) &#xA;service by any unauthorized person; or (f) other software used by Licensee &#xA;which has not been provided by Licensor or for which the Licensed Software is &#xA;not designed and licensed for operation; or (g) Third Party Software, as &#xA;defined below; or (h) any other cause occurring after initial delivery of the &#xA;media to Licensee unless caused directly by Licensor.  The foregoing states &#xA;the complete and entire remedies that Licensee has under this warranty.  &#xA;Licensor shall have no responsibility for any warranty claims made outside of &#xA;the Warranty Period.&#xA;8 DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY.  The Licensed Software cannot &#xA;be tested in every possible operating environment, therefore Licensor does &#xA;not warrant that the functions contained in the Licensed Software will meet &#xA;Licensee&apos;s requirements, that operation of the Licensed Software will be &#xA;uninterrupted, or that the Licensed Software is error free.  EXCEPT AS SET &#xA;FORTH HEREIN AND TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, &#xA;EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, &#xA;IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, QUALITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR &#xA;PURPOSE ARE EXCLUDED ON THE PART OF LICENSOR AND ITS THIRD-PARTY SUPPLIERS.  &#xA;Licensee acknowledges that Licensee is responsible for the selection of the &#xA;Licensed Software to achieve Licensee&apos;s intended results and for the &#xA;installation of, use of and results obtained from the Licensed Software.  &#xA;&#xA;9 LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.  ANY LIABILITY OF LICENSOR &#xA;SHALL BE LIMITED IN THE AGGREGATE TO THE AMOUNTS PAID BY LICENSEE FOR THE &#xA;LICENSED SOFTWARE.  THIS LIMITATION APPLIES TO ALL CAUSES OF ACTION, &#xA;INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION BREACH OF CONTRACT, BREACH OF WARRANTY, &#xA;NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, MISREPRESENTATION AND OTHER TORTS.  THE &#xA;LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY DESCRIBED IN THIS SECTION 9 ALSO APPLY TO LICENSOR&apos;S &#xA;THIRD-PARTY SUPPLIERS.  LICENSOR&apos;S AND ITS THIRD-PARTY SUPPLIERS&apos; LIMITATIONS &#xA;OF LIABILITY ARE NOT CUMULATIVE.  Licensee&apos;s remedies in this License &#xA;Agreement are Licensee&apos;s exclusive remedies.&#xA;NEITHER LICENSOR NOR ANY OF ITS THIRD-PARTY SUPPLIERS SHALL BE LIABLE &#xA;FOR ANY INJURY, LOSS OR DAMAGE, WHETHER INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR &#xA;CONSEQUENTIAL NOR FOR ANY LOST PROFITS, CONTRACTS, LOSS OF DATA OR PROGRAMS, &#xA;OR THE COST OF RECOVERING SUCH DATA OR PROGRAMS, EVEN IF INFORMED OF THE &#xA;POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES IN ADVANCE.  &#xA;NEITHER THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT NOR ANYTHING IN THIS SECTION 9 SHALL &#xA;PURPORT TO EXCLUDE OR RESTRICT THE LIABILITY OF LICENSOR OR ITS THIRD-PARTY &#xA;SUPPLIERS TO ANY EXTENT NOT PERMITTED BY LAW.  &#xA;10  HIGH-RISK USES.  The Licensed Software is not fault &#xA;tolerant, nor designed, manufactured or intended for use in hazardous &#xA;environments requiring fail-safe performance (including, without limitation, &#xA;the operation of nuclear facilities, aircraft navigation or communication &#xA;systems, air traffic control, direct life support machines, or weapons &#xA;systems) in which failure of the Licensed Software could lead directly or &#xA;indirectly to death, personal injury or severe physical or environmental &#xA;damage.  Licensor and its suppliers specifically disclaim any express or &#xA;implied warranty of fitness for a particular purpose and shall have no &#xA;liability for any use of the Licensed Software in any high-risk situations. &#xA;&#xA;11 OWNERSHIP.  Licensor (or its affiliates) and where &#xA;applicable Licensor&apos;s third party suppliers have and will retain all &#xA;ownership rights to the Licensed Software, together with any complete or &#xA;partial copies thereof. Such ownership rights include without limitation all &#xA;patent rights, copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, service marks, related &#xA;goodwill, and confidential and proprietary information relating thereto.  &#xA;This License Agreement does not convey any proprietary interest to Licensee &#xA;with respect to the Licensed Software other than the license specified &#xA;herein.  Where the Licensed Software provided under this License Agreement &#xA;contains or is derived from portions of materials provided by a third-party &#xA;supplier under license to Licensor, Licensor has assumed responsibility for &#xA;the selection of such materials and their use in producing the Licensed &#xA;Software and any such third-party suppliers are intended beneficiaries of &#xA;this License Agreement.  &#xA;12 NOTICE TO U.S. GOVERNMENT END USERS.  The Licensed &#xA;Software is provided to the United States Government with RESTRICTED RIGHTS &#xA;and its supporting documentation is provided with LIMITED RIGHTS.  Use, &#xA;duplication, or disclosure by the United States Government is subject to the &#xA;restrictions as set forth in FAR52.227-14 and DFAR252.227-7013 et seq. or the &#xA;successor as appropriate.  Manufacturer is Borland Software Corporation, 8310 &#xA;North Capital of Texas Highway, Building 2, Suite 100, Austin, TX 78731, &#xA;USA.&#xA;13 LICENSE FEES, PAYMENT, AND TERMS.  Licensee agrees to &#xA;pay the applicable end user license fees for the Licensed Software within &#xA;thirty (30) days of the date of invoice or such earlier date as is specified &#xA;in the Product Order.  End user license fees are non-refundable except as &#xA;provided in Section 7 above, or in the Specific Software Terms below, and &#xA;shall be paid without deduction, including without limitation, of any &#xA;withholding tax.  End user license fees are exclusive of any applicable &#xA;transportation charges, value added and other applicable taxes and duties and &#xA;all such amounts shall be paid or reimbursed by Licensee. Late payments shall &#xA;accrue interest at the rate of 1.5% per month compounded or, if lower, the &#xA;maximum rate allowed by law.  &#xA;14 RELATED SERVICES.  Licensee shall be responsible for &#xA;obtaining and installing all proper hardware and support software (including &#xA;operating systems) and for proper installation and implementation of and &#xA;training concerning the Licensed Software.  In the event that Licensee &#xA;retains Licensor to perform any services with respect to the Licensed &#xA;Software (for example: installation, implementation, maintenance, consulting &#xA;and/or training services), Licensee and Licensor agree that such services &#xA;shall be subject to Licensor&apos;s then current standard terms, conditions and &#xA;rates for such services unless otherwise agreed in writing by Licensor.&#xA;15 THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE AND COMPONENTS.  The Licensed &#xA;Software may contain certain named third party software programs that &#xA;Licensee shall license directly from the third party subject to such third &#xA;party&apos;s terms and conditions (for example Adobe Acrobat or Microsoft Internet &#xA;Explorer) (&apos;Third Party Software&apos;).  All Third Party Software is &#xA;provided by the licensor of the Third Party Software and solely under such &#xA;third party&apos;s terms and conditions and not by Licensor.   Therefore the &#xA;obligations, duties and rights of Licensor and Licensee under this License &#xA;Agreement do not apply to such Third Party Software.  Additionally, Licensor &#xA;has embedded certain run time or other elements provided by third party &#xA;suppliers to Licensor (&apos;Third Party Components&apos;). Such Third Party &#xA;Components may also be loaded on the Licensed Software media. Third Party &#xA;Components are licensed to Licensee pursuant to this License Agreement.  &#xA;Licensee may only access Third Party Components of the Licensed Software in &#xA;the course of using the Licensed Software.  Licensee may not make or attempt &#xA;any direct access to any such Third Party Components other than with the &#xA;Licensed Software. The Third-Party Software is the property of its respective &#xA;third party supplier to Licensor.  Such third party suppliers own all copies &#xA;of the Third-Party Software, however made. Licensee agrees not to contest the &#xA;ownership of the Third Party Components nor use any trademark or service mark &#xA;belonging to such third party suppliers. All limitations, restrictions and &#xA;obligations applicable to the Licensed Software set forth in this License &#xA;Agreement shall apply to Licensee&apos;s use of the Third Party Components.  &#xA;Licensee agrees that such third party suppliers are intended third party &#xA;beneficiaries of all terms and conditions of this License Agreement intended &#xA;to protect intellectual property rights in the Licensed Software (including &#xA;the Third Party Components) and limit certain uses thereof.&#xA;16 PRIVACY.  The Licensed Software may contain features &#xA;which may allow Licensee to collect data from, control and/or monitor &#xA;computers running the Licensed Software deployed by Licensee without notice &#xA;to or knowledge by users of the Licensed Software.  Licensee is solely &#xA;responsible for, and assumes all liability with respect to, the collection of &#xA;data with respect to its users of the Licensed Software including, without &#xA;limitation, notifying such users and complying with all data collection, &#xA;privacy and other regulations, laws, industry standards and rights of others &#xA;applicable to any such activity.  Licensee shall indemnify and hold Licensor &#xA;harmless from and against any damages, claims, losses, settlements, &#xA;attorneys&apos; fees, legal fees and court costs and other expenses related to any &#xA;such activities or any claims in connection therewith.  To the extent &#xA;permitted by law, by entering into this License Agreement, Licensee hereby &#xA;expressly consents to (i) Licensor sending information to Licensee from time &#xA;to time advertising the various products that Licensor provides, whether or &#xA;not such products are provided under this License Agreement; (ii) the use of &#xA;Licensee&apos;s name in Licensor customer lists, promotional materials and/or &#xA;press releases; and (iii) the collection and use by Licensor of information &#xA;about the computer system on which the Licensed Software is installed (e.g. &#xA;product version, serial number) for  internal security and licensing &#xA;purposes; Licensor does not use this information to identify individuals &#xA;utilizing such software.&#xA;17 MISCELLANEOUS. Licensor may assign this License &#xA;Agreement to any member of Licensor&apos;s group of companies or to a purchaser of &#xA;the intellectual property rights in the Licensed Software, but otherwise &#xA;neither this License Agreement nor any rights hereunder may be assigned (any &#xA;change of control merger, sale or other transfer of all, or substantially &#xA;all, of the assets of Licensee shall be included in the meaning of an &#xA;assignment) nor duties delegated by either party, and any attempt to do so &#xA;will be void.  If Licensee acquires the Licensed Software in North America, &#xA;the laws of the state of Maryland govern this License Agreement and it shall &#xA;be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the State of &#xA;Maryland.  If Licensee acquires the Licensed Software in France, Germany or &#xA;Japan, this License Agreement is governed by the laws of the country in which &#xA;Licensee acquired the Licensed Software.  In the rest of the world the laws &#xA;of England govern this License Agreement.  The aforesaid applicable law shall &#xA;apply without regard to conflicts of laws provisions thereof, and without &#xA;regard to the United Nations Convention on the International Sale of Goods.  &#xA;Other than for North American transactions, this License Agreement shall be &#xA;subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the country &#xA;determining the applicable law as aforesaid.  This License Agreement is in &#xA;addition expressly made subject to any United States, United Kingdom or &#xA;European Union laws, regulations and other restrictions regarding export or &#xA;re-export of computer software and technology.  Licensee agrees not to export &#xA;or re-export any Licensed Software or derivative thereof in contradiction to &#xA;any such applicable restriction.  Except for the Product Order, this License &#xA;Agreement is the complete and exclusive statement of agreement between the &#xA;parties relating to the license for the Licensed Software and supersedes all &#xA;proposals, communications, purchase orders, and prior agreements, verbal or &#xA;written, including without limitation prior end user license agreements in &#xA;relation to the Licensed Software between the parties and end user license &#xA;agreements embedded in such Licensed Software.  Upon Licensee&apos;s properly &#xA;authorized installation of any update and/or upgrade of any Licensed Software &#xA;licensed hereunder, the license granted to such prior version and/or release &#xA;shall terminate after a ninety (90) day transition period from such &#xA;installation and only the license to such updated and/or upgraded Licensed &#xA;Software shall continue.  No employee, agent, or representative of Licensor &#xA;has the authority to bind Licensor to any oral representation or warranty &#xA;concerning the Licensed Software.  No representation or statement not &#xA;expressly contained in this License Agreement nor any supplement, &#xA;modification, or amendment of this License Agreement will be binding on &#xA;either party unless executed in writing by a duly authorized representative &#xA;of each party to this License Agreement.  &#xA;ANNEX 1&#xA;A. LICENSE OPTIONS FOR THE FOLLOWING SOFTWARE PRODUCTS:&#xA;CaliberRMTM, TeamDefineTM, Together®, StarTeam®, TempoTM, TeamDemand®, &#xA;TeamFocusTM, TeamInspectorTM, SilkCentral®, Test ManagerTM, SilkTest®, &#xA;Silk4JTM, SilkPerformer® including portions thereof, other products within &#xA;the same product families and other Software Products where indicated by &#xA;Licensor.&#xA;&#xA;Regardless of the type of license, each copy of the Licensed Software &#xA;contains (i) software that provides services on a computer called a server &#xA;(&apos;Server Software&apos;) and (ii) software that allows a computer or &#xA;workstation to access or utilize the services provided by the Server Software &#xA;(&apos;Client Software&apos;). For any type of license acquired, Licensee may &#xA;install one copy of the Server Software on a single computer (the computer &#xA;running the Server Software shall be referred to as the &apos;Server&apos;). &#xA;The number of Client Software copies that may be installed is determined by &#xA;the type of license acquired as set forth below.&#xA;&#xA;1. Named User A Named User license means Licensee may &#xA;allow only one (1) designated person in Licensee&apos;s organization (&apos;Named &#xA;User&apos;) to use the Licensed Software per Named User license purchased &#xA;(each, a &apos;Named User License&apos;). The foregoing Named User Licenses &#xA;shall be for access and use, only by the equivalent number of Named Users &#xA;licenses purchased. For each Named User, Licensee may install the Client &#xA;Software on up to five (5) computers provided that the Named User is the only &#xA;individual permitted to use the Licensed Software.&#xA;&#xA;2. Concurrent User A Concurrent User License means &#xA;Licensee may install the Client Software on a reasonable number of computers &#xA;or machines, provided that the Licensed Software is used only by as many &#xA;concurrent users at any given moment in time as Licensee has purchased &#xA;concurrent licenses and provided further that Licensee&apos;s use of the Licensed &#xA;Software (both Client Software and Server Software) is only on computers or &#xA;machines located in the Territory and accessed only by users physically &#xA;located in the Territory. The foregoing license shall be for access and use, &#xA;only by the equivalent number of concurrent users for whom Licensee has paid &#xA;the applicable license fees. As used in this Section, use or in use means &#xA;that the Licensed Software is &quot;in use&quot; on a computer or machine when it is &#xA;loaded into random access memory (RAM) of that computer and &#xA;&apos;access&apos; means the ability to use, copy or operate the Licensed &#xA;Software . The Licensed Software may not be shared or used concurrently on &#xA;computers or machines located outside of the Territory or in such a way to &#xA;enable use or access by users located outside the Territory.  &apos;Territory&apos; &#xA;means the geographical area in which the Licensed Software may be used. The &#xA;use in the Territory shall be subject to applicable export restrictions. &#xA;Territory may be any one, and only one, of the following three geographic &#xA;areas: Americas Territory, EMEA Territory or AsiaPac Territory each as &#xA;defined below. The Territory shall be based on the primary business location &#xA;of the Licensor, unless otherwise specified in a Product Order. The &#xA;geographic Territories are: (i) &apos;Americas Territory&apos; including and limited to &#xA;those geographical areas found within the boundaries of North and South &#xA;America. (ii) &apos;Europe, Middle East and Africa Territory&apos; or &apos;EMEA Territory&apos; &#xA;including and limited to those geographical areas found within the boundaries &#xA;of Europe, Middle East and Africa, including all the countries which are part &#xA;of the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Jersey, Guernsey, Isle of Man, &#xA;Iceland, Monaco, Andorra, Liechtenstein, San Marino, Albania, all the &#xA;countries of the former Yugoslavia, Israel, Turkey, countries of the Arab &#xA;Middle East,  all the countries of the former Soviet Union, Africa, &#xA;Madagascar, and the Islands of the South Indian Ocean. (iii) &apos;Asia Pacific &#xA;Territory&apos; or &apos;AsiaPac Territory&apos; including and limited to those geographical &#xA;areas found within the boundaries of Asia and Australia/Pacific including &#xA;South Korea, Japan, China, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macau India, Maldives, &#xA;Pakistan, Myanmar, Nepal, Bhutan, Bangladesh, Thailand, Laos, Cambodia, &#xA;Vietnam, Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, East Timor, the Philippines, Brunei, &#xA;Papua New Guinea, the Pacific Ocean Islands, Australia, and New Zealand.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;3.  Virtual User (SilkPerformer only) A &quot;Virtual User&quot; &#xA;represents a simulation of a particular individual user executing a &#xA;transaction or sequence of operations. Virtual Users are further qualified by &#xA;class, and may be licensed on either a Node-Locked or Concurrent User basis. &#xA;If a Virtual User is licensed on a Node-Locked basis (as provided below) &#xA;(&apos;Node-Locked Virtual User License&apos;), that Virtual User may be &#xA;associated with a Multi-Machine Controller (&apos;MMC&apos;) component of the &#xA;Licensed Software only on the particular system for which the Virtual User is &#xA;licensed. If a Virtual User is licensed on a Concurrent User basis (as &#xA;provided below) (&apos;Concurrent Virtual User License&apos;), then that &#xA;Virtual User may be associated with any licensed instantiation of a MMC at &#xA;any one time, but during the operation of that instantiation, may not be &#xA;associated with any other instantiation of a MMC at the same time. By way of &#xA;example; if 50 Virtual Users are licensed on a Concurrent User basis, &#xA;Licensee may simultaneously associate all 50 with one MMC instantiation; or &#xA;simultaneously may associate 20 with one MMC instantiation and 30 with a &#xA;second MMC instantiation; but could not, for example, simultaneously &#xA;associate 30 with each of the two MMC instantiations. A &quot;Web Virtual User&quot; is &#xA;a Virtual User limited to performing actions in basic web-based applications &#xA;making use of the common web protocols set forth in the accompanying release &#xA;notes. A &quot;Standard Virtual User&quot; is a Virtual User that has all of the rights &#xA;of a Web Virtual User, and that may additionally make use of certain client-&#xA;server, database and other protocols as set forth in the accompanying release &#xA;notes. A &quot;Premium Virtual User&quot; is a Virtual User that has all of the rights &#xA;of a Standard Virtual User, and that may additionally make use of certain &#xA;protocols for packaged third-party applications and complex enterprise &#xA;technologies as set forth in the accompanying release notes.  Node-Locked &#xA;Virtual User Licenses and Concurrent Virtual User Licenses are available for &#xA;the MMC or Service Analysis Module (&apos;SAM&apos;) component of the &#xA;Licensed Software. A Node Locked Virtual User License means Licensee may use &#xA;the Licensed Software in object code form on a production basis on one (1) &#xA;computer and to permit the Licensed Software to be used and accessed at any &#xA;one time by no more than the number of users indicated in the applicable &#xA;Product Order (each a &quot;Node Locked User&quot;). If no number is indicated, the &#xA;number shall be 1.  A Concurrent Virtual User License means the same as the &#xA;Concurrent User license option above.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Notes(i) Multiplexing software:  The use of one or more &#xA;external tools, including multiplexors or replicators, to reduce the number &#xA;of users directly connected to the Licensed Software shall not exempt &#xA;Licensee from acquiring licenses for all users. For example, use of &#xA;multiplexing or connection pooling software or hardware to reduce the number &#xA;of users directly connected to the Licensed Software, the number of Named &#xA;Users or Concurrent Users within Licensee&apos;s organization using the Licensed &#xA;Software shall be measured as the number of distinct inputs to the &#xA;multiplexing or connection pooling front end and Licensee shall purchase the &#xA;equivalent number of Named User or Concurrent User Licenses. If Licensee uses &#xA;replicator software, Licensee may not use the Licensed Software or share &#xA;licenses in any way not explicitly provided for in this License Agreement.  &#xA;(ii) APIs: Any user of any third party application that &#xA;calls any Licensed Software application programming interfaces (&apos;Product &#xA;APIs&apos;) must have a valid license to connect to the Licensed Software. &#xA;Licensee shall not, and shall not allow others, to reverse engineer, &#xA;decompile, or disassemble the Product APIs. Commercial distribution of any &#xA;products that include Product APIs requires a separate distribution license &#xA;and such license is not granted by this License Agreement.  (iii) &#xA;TeamInspector:  TeamInspector is licensed on a Named User basis &#xA;only.  &#xA;B. LICENSE OPTIONS FOR THE FOLLOWING SOFTWARE &#xA;PRODUCTS:&#xA;&#xA;All Application Middleware products including AppServerTM and VisiBroker® &#xA;including portions thereof, other products within the same product families &#xA;and other Software Products where indicated by Licensor.&#xA;1. Development License Options&#xA;(a) Named User: For each Named User License, Licensee may &#xA;install and execute the Licensed Software on one (1) computer for use by one &#xA;(1) person in Licensee&apos;s organization solely to develop, compile (including &#xA;byte code compile), and test, in source or object code form, Licensee&apos;s own &#xA;application programs and other works (&quot;Works&quot;) designed to work with the &#xA;Licensed Software. Unless Licensee has purchased a valid Deployment License &#xA;as described below, Licensee may not deploy or use the Licensed Software on a &#xA;production basis. The Licensed Software contains certain time-out features &#xA;designed to prevent the Licensed Software from being deployed in a runtime &#xA;environment for longer than a specified period without Deployment License &#xA;keys. Deployment License keys will be provided to Licensee at such time as &#xA;Licensee purchases the requisite Deployment Licenses.  WORKS CREATED USING &#xA;THE LICENSED SOFTWARE MAY REQUIRE THE LICENSED SOFTWARE IN ORDER TO RUN. &#xA;WITHOUT THE REQUISITE DEPLOYMENT LICENSE KEYS, THE LICENSED SOFTWARE WILL BE &#xA;DISABLED AND THOSE WORKS MAY NO LONGER RUN. LICENSEE SHOULD THEREFORE TAKE &#xA;PRECAUTIONS TO AVOID ANY LOSS OF DATA THAT MIGHT RESULT.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;2. Deployment License Options&#xA;(a) Concurrent User: For each Concurrent User Deployment &#xA;License, License may install the Licensed Software, in executable form only, &#xA;on a server accessed and used by multiple users over a network, provided that &#xA;the Licensed Software is used only by as many concurrent users at any given &#xA;moment in time as Licensee has purchased concurrent licenses and provided &#xA;further that use of the Licensed Software is only in the Territory and &#xA;accessed only by users physically located in the Territory. The foregoing &#xA;license shall be for access and use, only by the equivalent number of &#xA;concurrent users for whom Licensee has paid the applicable license fees, &#xA;solely to create, compile (including byte code compile), test and deploy, in &#xA;source or object code form, Works. As used in this Section, use or in use &#xA;means that the Licensed Software is &quot;in use&quot; on a computer or machine when it &#xA;is loaded into random access memory (RAM) of that computer. The Licensed &#xA;Software may not be shared or used concurrently on computers or machines &#xA;located outside of the Territory or in such a way to enable use or access by &#xA;users located outside the Territory.&#xA;&#xA;(b) Server/CPU: For each Server/CPU Deployment License &#xA;Licensee may install and execute the Licensed Software in object code form on &#xA;a production basis on one (1) server hardware unit that is operating the &#xA;platform designated in the applicable Product Order and that has no more than &#xA;the number of CPUs designated in the applicable Product Order and to permit &#xA;the Licensed Software as so installed to be accessed at any one time by an &#xA;unlimited number of concurrent users. Licensee may not install or execute the &#xA;Licensed Software on any type of device that has a greater number of CPUs and &#xA;Licensee may not, under a given Server/CPU Deployment License, install or &#xA;execute the Licensed Software on more than one (1) computer. Licensee may use &#xA;and deploy the Licensed Software either as a Server or as a Client. Use of &#xA;the Licensed Software as a &quot;Server&quot; means to manage and control the automated &#xA;exchanges of information with one or more remote computers through various &#xA;telecommunications channels. Use of the Licensed Software as a &quot;Client&quot; means &#xA;to operate the Licensed Software on a computer to facilitate communications &#xA;with the Server. The Client shall not act as or perform the functions of a &#xA;Server.  A Client may make only a maximum of 10 concurrent call backs. A &#xA;Client shall not have POA (Portable Object Adapter) policies with the &#xA;following values:  &#xA;LifespanPolicyValue.PERSISTENT; &#xA;RequestProcessingPolicyValue.USE_SERVANT_MANAGER;&#xA;RequestProcessingPolicyValue.USE_DEFAULT_SERVANT&#xA;Subject to these restrictions and limitations and any additional &#xA;restrictions or limitations that may appear in the applicable Product Order, &#xA;Licensee may install the Client on an unlimited number of computers. Licensee &#xA;receives no right to deploy Clients without the purchase of a Server/CPU &#xA;Deployment License.&#xA;&#xA;(c) Backup Server License Option for AppServer and &#xA;VisiBroker Licensee may install the Licensed Software on a single &#xA;backup server and use the Licensed Software in object code form solely for &#xA;backup or disaster recovery purposes (&apos;Backup Server License&apos;). &#xA;Licensee may not use the Licensed Software on a production basis except &#xA;during periods when one or more copies of the Licensed Software for which &#xA;Licensee has purchased a Deployment License are nonfunctional, and, in such &#xA;event, only in accordance with the terms of the Deployment License.&#xA;&#xA;(d) Standby Server License Option for AppServer and &#xA;VisiBroker Licensee may install the Licensed Software on a single &#xA;standby server and use the Licensed Software in object code form solely in a &#xA;standby, non-production mode for use in the event the primary server fails &#xA;(&apos;Standby Server License&apos;). Licensee may not use the Licensed &#xA;Software on a production basis under a Standby Server License except during &#xA;periods when one or more copies of the Licensed Software for which Licensee &#xA;has purchased a Deployment License are nonfunctional, and, in such event, &#xA;only in accordance with the terms of the Deployment License.&#xA;&#xA;C. OTHER LICENSE OPTIONS &#xA;1. System Partitioning /LPAR/IFL Licensed Software may be &#xA;licensed for installation and use on computer systems which incorporate &#xA;logical partitioning (LPAR), and/or Integrated Facility for Linux &#xA;(&apos;IFL&apos;) provided such rights have been expressly granted to &#xA;Licensee by Licensor in writing and Licensee complies with the restrictions &#xA;set forth in this Section.  The licensing models in this Section 1 are only &#xA;applicable to Server type licenses and are not available for computer systems &#xA;where system resources (e.g. Cores/CPUs) may be scaled down or varied (e.g. &#xA;&apos;Pay Per Use&apos; or &apos;Pay Per Forecast&apos; models).&#xA;(a)  Logical Partitioning (LPAR):  The licensing &#xA;requirements of computer systems (e.g. a Host Server) which incorporate hard &#xA;and/or soft partitioning shall have their licensing requirements determined &#xA;as follows: &#xA;(i)  Hard Partitioning:  Hard partitioning is established &#xA;by using a hard physical partition to physically segment a single larger &#xA;server so that the Host Server utilizing the Licensed Software is a separate &#xA;and distinct smaller system (that is, each separate system acts as a &#xA;physically independent, self-contained server with its own CPUs, operating &#xA;system, separate boot area, memory, input/output subsystem and network &#xA;resources).  Examples of such hard partitioning include: Dynamic System &#xA;Domains (DSD) -- enabled by Dynamic Reconfiguration (DR), Solaris 10 &#xA;Containers (capped Containers only), LPAR (adds DLPAR with AIX 5.2), Micro-&#xA;Partitions (capped partitions only), vPar, nPar, Integrity Virtual Machine &#xA;(capped partitions only), Secure Resource Partitions (capped partitions &#xA;only), and Static Hard Partitioning.  For computer systems where hard &#xA;partitioning has been employed to create the Host Server being utilized to &#xA;operate the Licensed Software, such Host Server shall be licensed pursuant to &#xA;the terms and conditions set forth in this Section 1 as if such Host Server &#xA;where a separate and distinct computer system.  For example, where the total &#xA;computer system has 8 Cores/CPUs but only 4 Cores/CPUs have been hard &#xA;portioned to use the Licensed Software, Licensee shall only be required to &#xA;license such 4 Cores/CPUs on such hard partitioned system. &#xA;(ii)  Soft Partitioning:  Soft partitioning is &#xA;established by using the computer systems operating system resource manager &#xA;to segment and limit the number of Cores/CPUs where the Licensed Software is &#xA;running by creating areas where processor resources are allocated and limited &#xA;within the same operating system.  Examples of such soft partitioning &#xA;include: Solaris 9 Resource Containers, AIX Workload Manager, HP Process &#xA;Resource Manager, Affinity Management, Oracle VM, and VMware.  For computer &#xA;systems where soft partitioning has been employed to create the Host Server &#xA;being utilized to operate the Licensed Software, such Host Server shall be &#xA;licensed pursuant to the terms and conditions set forth in this Section 1 as &#xA;if such Host Server where a separate and distinct computer system but the &#xA;Cores/CPU required to be licensed shall be an &apos;expected&apos; Cores/CPU &#xA;number calculated as the ratio of the number of Cores/CPUs soft partitioned &#xA;as a percentage of the entire computer system&apos; Cores/CPUs, increased by ten &#xA;percent (10%).  For example, on an 8 Core/CPU computer system where soft &#xA;partitioning has been utilized such that only 4 Cores/CPUs are allocated to &#xA;use the Licensed Software, a Server License fee charge equal to 60% of the &#xA;total computer system Cores/CPUs would be required (50%+10% = 60% of an 8 &#xA;Core/CPU system license fee). &#xA;(b)  Integrated Facility for Linux (&apos;IFL&apos;):  An &#xA;Integrated Facility for Linux or IFL Host Server is established by using a &#xA;dedicated Host Server where the IFL Host Server is isolated from general use &#xA;and is only capable of utilizing the Linux operating system and running Linux &#xA;applications and cannot run other operating systems or applications.  For IFL &#xA;Host Server computer systems being utilized to operate the Licensed Software, &#xA;such IFL Host Server shall be licensed pursuant to the terms and conditions &#xA;set forth in this Section 1 as if such IFL Host Server were a separate and &#xA;distinct computer system.  For example, where the total computer system that &#xA;has 8 Cores/CPUs but the IFL Host Server is a 4 Cores/CPUs IFL computer &#xA;system and the IFL system is the only system using the Licensed Software, &#xA;Licensee shall only be required to license such 4 Cores/CPUs on such IFL Host &#xA;Server system. &#xA;(c )&#x9;LPAR and IFL Host Server Verification:  Licensee &#xA;shall provide to Licensor, upon commencement of this License Agreement and at &#xA;such other times as Licensor may reasonably request, confirmation that &#xA;Licensee&apos;s computer systems comply with the LPAR and/or IFL license &#xA;requirements set forth in Subsections 1(a) and (b) above. Such confirmation &#xA;shall be signed by a director or officer of Licensee and shall be accompanied &#xA;by all information as Licensor reasonably requires to verify that Licensee is &#xA;utilizing the Licensed Software in compliance with the terms and conditions &#xA;of the License Agreement. The foregoing is in addition to Licensor&apos;s rights &#xA;under Section 3 of the License Agreement.&#xA;2. Evaluation License Option Licensed Software provided &#xA;under this License Option gives Licensee a term license to use the Licensed &#xA;Software within Licensee&apos;s organization during the evaluation term specified &#xA;in writing by Licensor, solely for evaluation and testing purposes on a &#xA;single computer system and not for development, commercial, or production &#xA;purposes. Licensee may not reproduce or distribute the Licensed Software. &#xA;Licensee&apos;s results of benchmark or other performance tests run on or using &#xA;the Licensed Software may not be disclosed to any third party without &#xA;Licensor&apos;s prior written consent. At any time during the evaluation term or &#xA;upon completion thereof, Licensee may, upon written notification to Licensor &#xA;and payment of the applicable license fee, replace the evaluation license &#xA;with a license to use the Licensed Software pursuant to one of the other &#xA;applicable options listed in Annex1.  In the absence of such notification by &#xA;Licensee, the evaluation license shall automatically terminate at the end of &#xA;the evaluation term and Licensee shall return, or, if Licensor so directs, &#xA;delete and destroy all such Licensed Software and provide Licensor with &#xA;written confirmation of such deletion and destruction being completed. &#xA;Licensor may, in its sole discretion, grant Licensee an extension to the &#xA;evaluation term subject to receiving a written request and reasons for such &#xA;request from Licensee prior to expiration of the evaluation term. Licensor &#xA;will specify any such agreed extension in writing to Licensee. Licensed &#xA;Software provided by Licensor free of license fee charge shall be deemed to &#xA;be provided pursuant to this Evaluation License Option unless otherwise &#xA;agreed in writing. In the absence of any contrary period specified in writing &#xA;by Licensor, the evaluation term shall be deemed to be thirty (30) days. In &#xA;relation to Licensed Software provided pursuant to this Evaluation License &#xA;Option, this Section shall prevail over any contrary provisions set forth in &#xA;this License Agreement unless specifically provided otherwise.&#xA;3. Test License Option Licensed Software provided under &#xA;this License Option gives Licensee a limited license to use the Licensed &#xA;Software solely for Licensee&apos;s internal testing purposes on a single computer &#xA;system. At no time may Licensee use the Licensed Software for development, &#xA;commercial, or production purposes, nor may Licensee reproduce or distribute &#xA;the Licensed Software or any software application programs created with it. &#xA;The applicable license fee for this License Option will be determined by the &#xA;access or use to be tested. For example, batch process testing will require &#xA;the payment of the applicable license fee for a Licensor server license for &#xA;CPU. Licensee&apos;s results of benchmark or other performance tests run on or &#xA;using the Licensed Software may not be disclosed to any third party without &#xA;Licensor&apos;s prior written consent.  If Licensee uses the Test Licenses for any &#xA;purpose other than for Licensee&apos;s internal testing purposes, the Test License &#xA;shall terminate automatically and without notice.  Upon such termination, &#xA;Licensee may convert the terminated Test License to a standard license type &#xA;listed above by paying the applicable conversion fee.  In relation to &#xA;Licensed Software provided pursuant to this Test License Option, this Section &#xA;shall prevail over any contrary provisions set forth in this License &#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;ANNEX 2  SPECIFIC SOFTWARE TERMS&#xA;The following terms and conditions apply to the applicable Licensed &#xA;Software products named below and supersede any conflicting terms and &#xA;conditions set forth elsewhere in this License Agreement:&#xA;ACADEMIC EDITIONS/USER  This Licensed Software may be &#xA;used solely for Licensee&apos;s personal use in providing or receiving instruction &#xA;within the limited scope of guided computer programming and/or software &#xA;training course(s) in which Licensee is a direct and personal participant, &#xA;either as student or instructor (&apos;Course(s)&apos;). The Licensed &#xA;Software may only be used with other participants of the Courses and then &#xA;only for educational or training purposes. The Licensed Software may not be &#xA;used for any commercial, business, governmental or institutional purpose of &#xA;any kind, except to the extent Licensee is an instructor teaching a Course. &#xA;&#xA;SILKCENTRAL, TEST MANAGER, SILKTEST, SILK4J, &#xA;SILKPERFORMER  This Licensed Software may include technology for &#xA;monitoring authorized use, including the policy files and license keys &#xA;required to use the Licensed Software (the &apos;License Authorization &#xA;Server&apos; or &apos;LAS&apos;).  The LAS may be installed on a single-&#xA;specified computer system at the specific site for which Licensee has &#xA;contracted (the &apos;Designated System&apos;). The LAS, or any part thereof, &#xA;may not be transferred from the Designated System. Regardless of the &#xA;installation of the LAS, Licensee must remain compliant with the terms in &#xA;this License Agreement (including without limitation any license restrictions &#xA;and number of users permitted pursuant to this License Agreement).  The LAS &#xA;cannot be used or installed on a Virtual Machine.&#xA;&#xA;SILK PERFORMER. This Licensed Software may be installed &#xA;on a reasonable number of Licensee computer systems. Licensee may use the &#xA;Multi-Machine Controller (also referred to as &apos;Workbench&apos;) &#xA;(&apos;MMC&apos;) component and related load-test agents on an unlimited &#xA;number of machines for an unlimited number of users, but solely in connection &#xA;with the use of SilkPerformer in accordance with the number, type and class &#xA;of Virtual User Licenses purchased.  Premium Virtual User Licenses for &#xA;SilkPerformer, when ordered in any quantity, include a single Named User &#xA;limited license to use SilkTest (the &apos;Additional Product&apos;). The &#xA;Additional Product may be used ONLY in conjunction with the Premium Virtual &#xA;User Licenses of SilkPerformer and may not be used or transferred on a stand-&#xA;alone basis. Incremental use of any Additional Product beyond the single &#xA;Named User license, or stand-alone use, must be licensed and paid for &#xA;separately.&#xA;&#xA;TOGETHER.  This Licensed Software may be used solely to &#xA;create, compile (including byte code compile), test and deploy, in source or &#xA;object code form, Licensee application programs and other works. This &#xA;Licensed Software requires registration with Licensor prior to use. Licensee &#xA;will be prompted to register at the time of installation or first use, at &#xA;which time Licensee will be notified, or directed to online resources &#xA;explaining, how registration information provided by Licensee may be used and &#xA;Licensee will be afforded the opportunity to opt out of certain uses of such &#xA;information. Licensee may use the License Manager component of the Licensed &#xA;Software, in executable form only, on a server for use solely in connection &#xA;with Licensee&apos;s use of the Licensed Software.&#xA;&#xA;TEAMDEFINE. This Licensed Software includes the &#xA;capability for an unlimited number of users to review the simulation program &#xA;integrated into the Licensed Software by Licensor or its suppliers. Such &#xA;users may not otherwise use the Licensed Software.  Where an evaluation &#xA;license option is obtained for this Licensed Software pursuant to Annex 1.C.2 &#xA;the evaluation period will continue for up to 365 days. During the first 30 &#xA;days of the evaluation period Licensee will be able to access all &#xA;functionality of this Licensed Software except &apos;Project Export&apos;. &#xA;During the remaining evaluation period such functionality will continue &#xA;except that Licensee will have read only access to &apos;simulations&apos;, &#xA;&apos;requirements&apos;, &apos;SDK&apos;, &apos;integrations&apos;, &#xA;&apos;images&apos; and &apos;templates&apos;. Licensee may purchase a full &#xA;license for this Licensed Software at any time during the evaluation period. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;SILKCENTRAL, TEST MANAGER, SILKTEST, SILK4J, SILKPERFORMER, &#xA;TEAMDEFINE, CALIBER, TOGETHER, STARTEAM, TEMPO, TEAMDEMAND, TEAMFOCUS, &#xA;TEAMINSPECTOR, APPSERVER, VISIBROKER. This Licensed Software may be &#xA;used in a Virtual Machine only where a concurrent user license has been &#xA;granted&#xA;&#xA;APPSERVER, VISIBROKER. For this Licensed Software, &#xA;regardless of the number of CPU&apos;s for which Licensee has purchased a &#xA;Deployment License: (i) Licensee may not run more than one instance of the &#xA;deployed Licensed Software on a single computer, and (ii) the Licensed &#xA;Software may not be accessed at any one time by more than the number of &#xA;Concurrent Users indicated in the applicable Product Order. In the event &#xA;Licensee desire additional instances or additional Concurrent Users, Licensee &#xA;must purchase a separate license applicable to a different computer.&#xA;&#xA;APPLICATION MIDDLEWARE PRODUCTS.  Licensee may not &#xA;include this Licensed Software or any component thereof in any general-&#xA;purpose software development tool, library, component, or any other product &#xA;that is generally competitive with or a substitute for the Licensed Software &#xA;or any other Licensor product offerings; nor may Licensee use the Licensed &#xA;Software to create a product or operate a service that is generally &#xA;competitive with the Licensed Software or any other Licensor product &#xA;offerings, including any general-purpose software development tool. The &#xA;foregoing restriction does not apply, however, to use of the Licensed &#xA;Software to develop &quot;plug-ins&quot; (i.e., integrations created using the Licensed &#xA;Software&apos;s open tools API) so long as such plug-ins are designed to provide &#xA;supplementary functionality to the Licensed Software.  &#xA;&#xA;This Licensed Software is not redistributable. Licensee is not permitted &#xA;to reproduce the Licensed Software for sublicensing, resale, lending, &#xA;leasing, deployment or distribution to any party, including without &#xA;limitation, distributing the Licensed Software as part of a VAR, OEM, &#xA;distributor or reseller arrangement. If Licensee integrates the Licensed &#xA;Software into a Work and intends to distribute or resell the resulting &#xA;integrated Work, Licensee must contact Licensor to obtain the appropriate &#xA;distribution license.&#xA;&#xA;The portions of this Licensed Software identified as  VISISECURE,  &#xA;VISITRANSACT,  VISINOTIFY,  VISITIME and  VISITELCOLOG (collectively, the &quot; &#xA;VISISERVICES&quot;) are not redistributable. This License Agreement does not &#xA;permit Licensee to execute, or otherwise use the  VISISERVICES portion of the &#xA;Licensed Software for any purpose unless Licensee has acquired a separate &#xA;Development and/or Deployment License for  VISISERVICES directly from &#xA;Licensor before developing or deploying any Work that uses such portion of &#xA;the Licensed Software. Licensee is not permitted to reproduce  VISISERVICES &#xA;for sublicensing, resale, lending, leasing, deployment or distribution to any &#xA;party, including without limitation, distributing VISISERVICES as part of a &#xA;VAR, OEM, distributor or reseller arrangement. If Licensee integrates  &#xA;VISISERVICES into a Work and intends to distribute or resell the resulting &#xA;integrated Work, Licensee must contact Licensor to obtain the appropriate &#xA;distribution license.&#xA;&#xA;Notwithstanding the prohibition hereunder against decompiling this &#xA;Licensed Software, Licensee may use that portion of the Licensed Software &#xA;identified as &quot;API Decompiler&quot; for inspecting the public application &#xA;programming interface (API) of the JAVA BEANS COMPONENT LIBRARY, DATAEXPRESS, &#xA;DBSWING and OPENTOOLS API modules.&#xA;&#xA;The following Java Technology Restrictions are applicable to the component &#xA;of this Licensed Software identified as SonicMQ if it accompanies the &#xA;Licensed Software: Licensee may not modify the Java Platform Interface &#xA;(&quot;JPI&quot;, identified as classes contained within the &quot;java&quot; package or any &#xA;subpackages of the &quot;java&quot; package), by creating additional classes within the &#xA;JPI or otherwise causing the addition to or modification of the classes in &#xA;the JPI. In the event that Licensee otherwise create an additional class and &#xA;associated API(s) which (i) extends the functionality of a Java platform, and &#xA;(ii) is exposed to third party software developers for the purpose of &#xA;developing additional software which invokes such additional API, Licensee &#xA;must promptly publish broadly an accurate specification for such API for free &#xA;use by all developers. Licensee may not create, or authorize its own &#xA;licensees to create additional classes, interfaces, or subpackages that are &#xA;in any way identified as &quot;java&quot;, &quot;javax&quot;, &quot;sun&quot; or similar convention as &#xA;specified by sun in any class file naming convention.&#xA;&#xA;This Licensed Software may include certain files, libraries and/or source &#xA;code specifically designated as &apos;redistributables&apos; by Licensor in &#xA;the accompanying printed or on-line documentation and that are necessary to &#xA;use works created using the Product (&quot;Redistributables&quot;). From time to time, &#xA;Licensor may designate other files as Redistributables. Subject to the terms &#xA;and conditions of this License Agreement, Licensee may freely redistribute &#xA;source code or compiled code that is entirely Licensee&apos;s own and does not &#xA;contain any Redistributables. Subject to the terms and conditions of this &#xA;License Agreement, Licensor grants Licensee the personal, non-exclusive, non-&#xA;transferable and limited license to: (a) make exact copies of the &#xA;Redistributables and distribute those copies solely as components of &#xA;Licensee&apos;s Works and solely as required for permitting end users of the Works &#xA;(&apos;End users&quot;) to install and execute the Works; (b) install and execute &#xA;Redistributables, without modification, solely for Licensee&apos;s own internal &#xA;use; and (c) sublicense to End Users the personal, non-exclusive, non-&#xA;transferable right to install and execute Redistributables, without &#xA;modification, solely as components of Works and solely for such End Users&apos; &#xA;own internal use, subject to End Users&apos; compliance with the restrictions in &#xA;this License Agreement. These rights granted may not be exercised by others, &#xA;including co-developers, regardless of how Licensee&apos;s Works are compiled, &#xA;linked, or packaged. These rights apply only to Redistributables and to no &#xA;other file, library, source code or other component or derivative work of the &#xA;Licensed Software. They may be exercised only with respect to works created &#xA;by Licensee using a duly licensed, properly registered copy of the Licensed &#xA;Software.&#xA;'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='2'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam_3.5.feature.group' version='11.0.0.97v20111028-1643'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='10'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.eclipse.platform.feature.group' range='[3.5.0,4.0.0)'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam.sdk' range='[11.0.0.73,11.0.0.73]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam.sdk.native' range='[11.0.0.73,11.0.0.73]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam.gui' range='[11.0.0.81,11.0.0.81]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam.extensions' range='[11.0.0.017,11.0.0.017]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.team.starteam.provider' range='[11.0.0.97v20111028-1643,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.team.starteam.provider.ui' range='[11.0.0.97v20111028-1643,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.team.starteam.ui.integration' range='[11.0.0.97v20111028-1643,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.team.starteam.doc.user' range='[11.0.0.97v20111028-1643,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam_3.5.feature.jar' range='[11.0.0.97v20111028-1643,11.0.0.97v20111028-1643]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <filter>
        (&amp;(|(osgi.os=linux)(osgi.os=solaris)(osgi.os=win32)(osgi.os=macosx))(|(osgi.ws=gtk)(osgi.ws=motif)(osgi.ws=win32)(osgi.ws=carbon))(|(osgi.arch=sparc)(osgi.arch=x86)(osgi.arch=x86_64)))
      </filter>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.borland.starteam.sdk' version='11.0.0.73' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.borland.starteam.sdk' range='[0.0.0,11.0.0.73)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam.sdk' version='11.0.0.73'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.borland.starteam.sdk' version='11.0.0.73'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.borland.starteam.sdk' version='11.0.0.73'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='2'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.borland.starteam.sdk&#xA;Bundle-Version: 11.0.0.73&#xA;Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.borland.starteam.extensions' version='11.0.0.017' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.borland.starteam.extensions' range='[0.0.0,11.0.0.017)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.borland.starteam.extensions' version='11.0.0.017'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.borland.starteam.extensions' version='11.0.0.017'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.borland.starteam.extensions' version='11.0.0.017'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='2'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.borland.starteam.extensions&#xA;Bundle-Version: 11.0.0.017&#xA;Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
  </units>
</repository>
